Good evening.
Or morning.
Or whatever time it is for you.
How's everybody, huh?
I see you saw the new animated emoji I put in.
I kind of want to remove the white background, make it transparent, but I don't know how to do it.
I can do it in a picture, but not in a gif.
I don't know why.
I have to figure it out.
Good day!
What's up, Yujiri?
Lymanate, good to see you.
Raven Warrior.
Frank.
Hamadude, how are you?
Diego!
Hey, what's up, man?
Are you actually Diego?
I don't know your Twitch username.
If you are, prove it to me and send me a message right now.
Doing dandy?
I love it.
Dandy's good.
So I did something.
I'll show you.
I made a preliminary, very basic and very rough outline of the Noiter world as I know it.
Hold on.
Let me just slowly get rid of that.
There we go.
And go to here.
What?
What just happened?
A weird sound just played on my game closed.
Eh?
Hold on.
My game just closed down.
I have no idea what just happened.
Let me open again.
What the hell?
Isn't that?
That's like a meme.
Is that like a sound Noiter plays when it crashes?
Because I've heard that sound effect before.
Somewhere.
That's so weird.
Maybe that's like an Easter egg.
Oh, hold on.
There we go.
Okay, I just had to grab my phone.
It is you, Diego.
I see your message.
Okay.
I hereby bestow upon you.
Wait, how do I do it?
There you go.
The mod permissions have been granted onto the...
Does it work now?
Come on, game.
There we go.
Hey, it's working.
All right, so check this out.
Where's my thing?
And let me also do that.
So I made a very rough outline.
This is like the end.
I still explored more on the right side here, but I couldn't really remember what that was like.
But I found this place with the lava.
This is the music thing on the right.
And then we have a pyramid right there.
And then we keep going.
We have the pond with the music thing.
This is the beginning.
I spent way too much time on this, by the way.
I looked through the vod to get this sort of precise, you know.
So we have the little floating platform up there and the mountain, the hemisphere, of course, where the roots go into it from the tree.
And we have a music thing up here.
And there's definitely more I missed, but I don't remember all of it.
And then a bunch of stuff and the little hut in the lake with the containers.
So that's pretty much what I've done.
And I can show you here as well.
This is the hemisphere, right?
I don't really... because these are sort of randomized.
I know they're sort of on top of each other, so I've just sort of organized them like this.
Cold pits, snowy depths, heezy base, jungle, and I honestly don't remember the names of the ones coming afterward.
But I'll have to fill this out as I go.
I just don't remember what they're called.
And I couldn't be bothered to go through the vod and look for the exact moment when the text comes up to get the name of it.
So yeah, this is pretty much what I've had so far.
Yeah, I call this the hemisphere.
I like that a lot.
Very good.
So that's what I've got so far.
And here, you can even see, if I zoom in, I intend to put little icons.
You know, like this is a health upgrade and there's a little tablet next to it, a green one.
You know, pretty neat.
I think I... oh, I actually missed something in here.
I remember when I found this stone with the writing on the left, you could actually make a little hole and you could get to the music thingy, the music wand or whatever.
I didn't fill that out yet, but yeah, that'll come later.
Of course, then I also have my notes.
These are just very... I just put down a couple just to explain how I will do this, just to illustrate.
This is how it's going to look.
You know, I have some basic stuff I want to do, but before we get to any of that, we can't really do any of it, because I need to sort of get going first.
You know, I need to become strong.
I need to have a good wand, a lot of HP, and then we can do some proper exploration.
And you know what?
Just getting strong itself is proper exploration, because we haven't discovered all the perks yet.
And we have not found all the spells.
There's still a bunch of things to do.
So that's the plan.
That is the plan.
Okay.
Your handwriting is so good.
Thank you, man.
Thank you, I appreciate it.
That's what a lot of German school does to you.
They forced me to learn it.
If you want to see more of that, at the last episode of Hollow Knight, I actually put in the comments section a link to all of my notes I took during Hollow Knight.
Probably the last time I'll ever take physical notes, because I've discovered the joy of digital notes ever since.
But yeah, that one is also filled with a lot of that handwriting, if you're into that.
Okay.
I think I'm just gonna... What's up, Yuxo?
How's it going?
Thank you, Diego.
Thank you very much.
What program do you use for the notes?
I use a program called Journal.
But the J is spelled with an X instead.
It's kind of cringe.
But it works.
It does the job.
It's very basic.
It's not really fast at all.
It's a little bit slow.
Choppy, but it works.
I think it would be more optimal to use something like Photoshop, honestly.
But this is doing the job.
I used this for tuning as well.
It was really nice.
Okay.
Oh, real quick.
Is there a place to recommend games, like on Discord?
Yes, there is.
There's a games channel.
There's also a backlogged profile you can find of me, where you can see what games is already on my backlog, so you don't recommend a game that's already on there.
Okay.
I'm gonna close you guys down.
Hold on.
It means I have to click this.
No offense.
People always... I feel like whenever I say I'm gonna close you guys down, it always feels... I don't know, offensive or something.
Like, I don't want to look at you, you know?
Like, get away from me.
It's not like that at all, I swear.
I just want to focus on the game, that's all.
Okay.
Here we go.
I'll see you on the other side.
So, I was in the middle of a run, it seems?
No, I was not.
Well, technically I was, but not really, you know?
Let's see, we have spark bolts and bombs.
Okay.
Hold on, I just want to pull this up real quick again, because it's so cool.
Boop!
And then I can change it while doing things.
I can ride things.
Pretty cool stuff, I would say.
Alright, just wanted to illustrate that once more, if anyone just joined.
I have new capabilities.
Riding has been unlocked.
Map making skills unlocked.
Even though it's a very basic map.
So, I actually kind of want to pay attention to the layout of things as well, as I go along here.
Because I want to fill out the map with more detail.
There's a bunch of things I haven't added to the map yet, but I know are there.
You know, like, I know there's a dark area to the west in the hemisphere.
But I don't remember exactly where it is, so I have to sort of see it again.
Okay, we've got a dude there.
Alright, man.
That guy is gone already.
Oh, he's back.
And I'm on fire.
And I have a snow potion.
Snow doesn't do the trick, does it?
Shit.
Just let it fall on me.
Okay, that works.
You gotta shower yourself with the snow.
My god, man.
Are there two of them?
That's insanity.
Bro, welcome to Noita.
Welcome back, bitch.
That's like the game right now.
Man, oh, man.
I'm gonna blow you up.
Oh, shit.
I thought that was gonna roll down on him.
Whoops.
And we've got music as well.
This is a very high octane start, and there's a heart, too!
What the hell?
I'll take it.
That's definitely a nice thing to have.
In that case, I don't mind the fire dudes.
I really don't.
Hey, you!
I think I hit him for a lot there.
Whoa!
He's dead.
I really should pour water on him somehow.
Ah, the other one is right there.
What about snow?
I think I tried it once, but I don't remember.
Oh, he's definitely taking damage!
Look at that!
Snow is raining on him.
Heck yeah.
Hey, where are you?
I think he died!
That worked wonders.
Put the snow in here.
Then we mix it.
Oops.
No, no, no!
There we go.
Mix it all up.
Now we have water.
Why am I getting poisoned all the time?
Am I standing on a little pixel of poison?
Okay, there we go.
Maximum water.
Oh my god, there's more HP.
This is a great one so far.
Don't want to drain this, because there's all this water.
Kind of just want to enter from the bottom.
Oh wait, how am I going to do this?
Probably if I put it right there.
Shit!
Oh well.
Okay, if I put it right...
Nah, I'm going to drain it.
Don't take any chances, I have one bomb left.
Isn't this the coolest?
I think it is.
Oh my god, it's somehow blocked again.
That's berserkium, we want that in our blood for sure.
Then we can crit a lot.
Oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit.
Berserkium.
Nice, nice, nice, nice.
Dude, the berserkium is actually doing a lot of work here.
This is the good stuff.
There's a wand.
Not a bad start!
By the way, did I ever get that hard?
I did, I did.
I did pick it up.
We need water here.
We need to mix things.
It's so cool that you can sort of use your wand as a catalyst for this chemical reaction between water and toxic sludge.
See, I can't get in there now, that's an issue.
I can't get in here either.
I gotta find a wand with some bombs on it.
Or anything that will let me dig.
That is my current mission.
Let's just get rid of that.
Is it actually helping that I'm shooting it?
It is, right?
I'm definitely not imagining that.
It totally is simulated.
The actual particle of my wand is interacting with the particles in the water, mixing them up.
And you know what?
I don't even think that was intended.
I think that's just a result of all the...
What do you call it?
Interactive elements of the game, which is awesome.
They just made everything interactive, and then...
Okay, this is what happens when we do that, you know?
I'm not sure, I'm just guessing, but I'm guessing that's how that works.
I can get through here.
I don't want to go into Holy Mountain.
I'm kind of stuck here.
No, I can go through here.
I can get rid of that.
Oh, wait a minute.
No, no, no, no.
I was about to say, if this is made of wood, but it isn't, it's made of steel.
I could set fire to it.
This is something I have to remember.
All these hammers is...
Ow!
Oh my god, there's multiple!
That thing just... multiplied itself, times three.
One hammers became three hammers.
Almost sounds like a children's song, you know?
One hammers, two hammers, three hammers, go.
They want to catch you before you die, bro.
I don't even know what I'm trying to say here.
I wish I had telekinetic kick.
I want to be able to pick things up with my mind.
Give me more water.
Just fill it up completely.
Man, we lost so much HP already.
Bad start, bad start.
Actually, it's not a bad start.
We got two fucking hearts.
That's really nice.
I can't complain.
I cannot complain.
This is good.
There's a guy up here.
Come here.
Oh my god, the corpse is in the way.
That guy's scary.
And he drips poison on me.
We're fine.
Look at how that eats through the ground.
I kind of want that.
I can get that.
Hey, miss.
Almost shot that box to destruction there would have been a disaster.
There's way more hammers than usual.
Nice.
This is my shot.
Can I get it?
Can I get something nice?
Give me a digging wand.
Yes!
There we go.
That should do fine work here.
Freezing liquid, no thanks.
Freezing liquid is bad for you.
It is known.
All right, guys.
One at a time.
Form an orderly line.
Good.
Five hundred monies already.
Not bad.
I just got to play insanely careful for the rest of this hemisphere expedition.
I kind of want to find more of those puzzles.
I don't even know if you can call it a puzzle, but...
The oil puzzle that we had was so cool.
I want more.
I'm addicted to mixing this.
It's the best feeling.
It's like I'm cleansing the world.
Okay, so hold on.
Let me see the layout here.
This may actually always be like that.
I feel like it's always bending like this.
I could add that to the map, I guess.
Whoa!
Oi!
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit!
Okay, it's fine.
It's fine.
We lost a bit of HP.
It was all in the name of gold!
Not bad, not bad.
21 HP, that's doable.
It's like a little under a quarter of what we started with.
Could have been worse.
So where do we want to dig?
We saw a wand, right?
See, where was that?
I guess it was somewhere over here, because to the left is a place we haven't explored yet.
Maybe down?
Yeah, somewhere here.
I remember this, Berserkium.
There it is.
So I'm going to dig through from the top.
Boink!
Get that out of there.
Oh, wait, what?
Wait.
Huh?
Wait a minute, why are these...
Why are these red?
Oh, because...
Shit!
Wow!
Because I'm affected by Berserkium, that's why.
Because that looked like the exact same effect as when you put the plus damage on it.
But that's not what just happened, okay.
I understand.
In fact, did that increase my digging capability when I had that?
Wait a minute now.
Let me grab that Berserkium.
I need to test this real quick.
That's not a lot, unfortunately.
Is it going to be enough?
Ten percent?
Eight percent?
As long as I don't touch ground.
It's going to take a bit.
Unless it's better to go from the bottom.
Maybe right here.
That seems like a short distance.
Oh, this is painful.
It's working!
There could be an immense spell in this wand.
That's why we have to get it.
Is that not doing anything?
Hold on.
I need to be at a distance.
Give me... As long as I get to the ground here, I see dirt.
So I'm trying to dig through rock right now, but the remaining is actually ground.
So that should be quick.
Oh yeah, look at that, look at that.
Now we're speeding up.
Get in there.
Really should save my bombs.
That I have for something like this, you know.
I mean, I kind of did, but then I fucked it up.
Oh, what can I get?
No, not yet.
That should be enough.
Nope, not quite.
Oh, come on, man.
Where is the issue?
Right there.
I mean, not bad.
Thanks.
I like the double.
The double is good.
I think that was worth it.
Now, I could also get in here.
But...
I'm going to keep exploring.
Get some water.
Where did all these hammers come from?
They weren't here last time.
Even one hammers can kill me.
Just be real careful there.
Okay, let me see here.
So now I have this effect on me.
That is definitely digging faster.
Look.
Right?
The circular makes you dig faster.
Let me go below, actually.
I hear another portal.
In fact, I think those portals are always lined up in the same manner.
I keep thinking sort of randomized where they are, but I don't think it is.
Here I can get through easily.
What?
Not an issue.
I got to be super careful here.
Oh, hammers.
What else?
Oh, I'm going to destroy that.
Yes, sir.
I'm scared of fire right now.
Well, when am I not scared of fire?
Oh, shit!
Oh!
I got blown up and shot straight into the fire.
That's unreal.
Holy shit.
Wow.
Well, all right.
There it is.
I feel like, you know, I needed that anyway.
I needed to die once here.
Now I can sort of focus.
Now we got that death out of the way.
You know?
No biggie.
Let's go up and grab the extra HP now.
And now we're going to play for real, okay?
That was just a get back into the game run.
You know how it is.
Okay, that has a very surprising lack of range.
It's going to take a while.
It's working.
Dude, if I made a game, I would make the sound effects so fun.
Imagine every time you shot the wand, your character would go...
I don't know why.
That shit cracks me up.
Uh oh.
Oh, that just rolls off.
Weird.
Can I actually just fly up there?
Almost.
Maybe with some...
Maybe this will give me a bit of...
Oh yeah, it totally does.
A little bit, I guess.
Dammit, I'm going to use all of my stuff on this now.
I didn't expect this to be this bad.
I thought it would go a little quicker here.
Is that lava falling down?
Okay, slowly.
But surely.
I don't care about the tablet.
I just want that health.
Up!
Come on, one more, one more.
Whoa, there we go.
Yoink!
Familiar orb of true knowledge.
I wonder if that was called familiar the very first time I found it.
Or was it just called you found an orb of true knowledge?
I also wonder why it's called of true knowledge.
Right?
Why is it called true knowledge?
Am I getting closer to the truth by attaining these?
Orbs?
Whatever the truth is.
Can I even handle the truth?
Okay.
Systematic this time.
No more going all about.
Top floor first, all the way through, and then we go down one level.
Oh god, he's hidden behind that little wooden peg.
Okay.
Can't go any further.
There, so we go down.
We need to find the most optimal way through this place.
Because I'm here a lot, you know?
The hemisphere is... is my home.
It is.
Aha!
And I have water!
The hell is going on there?
Why is there just... that's weird.
Is that a fire dude?
I hear flames.
It is, I see him, I see him.
Ah, this is bad.
Ah!
He exploded?
No, there he is, there he is.
Let's water him a little bit.
Wow, he died instantly from that!
Holy shit!
I feel like usually they take more damage before they die.
Maybe he took some damage beforehand.
Somehow.
I'm gonna water this guy too.
Come here.
Come here, buddy.
Wanna
be right below me, that's right.
He's taking damage?
He is taking damage!
Yes, dude!
Water is totally the way to go with these.
I mean, I knew it already, but...
It's actually surprisingly easy to deal with them with water.
If you know what you're doing.
I feel like I'm not gonna lose any HP to those guys ever again, because of my newfound technique.
What is that?
Just gold lying on the ground?
What?
Huh!
In fact, let me...
No, let me not.
Let me not waste my digging capabilities on a measly amount of gold!
Fucking horta is hurting me.
Slime potion?
Sure.
Right, there's also an area called collapsed mines.
So that is all...
No, that is actually to the west of...
mines.
So on my map, I would have to put...
Wait, that means...
the dark area is to the west of collapsed mines.
Okay.
Gotcha.
Let me just do that.
Nice.
And again,
we keep it systematic, we keep exploring as high as we can, then we go all the way to the right again.
At the next...
lowest...
elevation.
Here we can get through easily.
Boop!
So wait,
where are the tree roots?
I kind of want to put things in perspective for the map.
Are the tree roots below the collapsed mines then?
Because I haven't seen them yet.
We've got frogs...
that have so much HP for some reason.
It scared me a little bit the way it just suddenly jumped.
I was considering how to get to him without taking damage.
But that problem solved itself.
Aha!
I can get through there.
In fact, let me use this.
Burn it.
While that's burning...
Oh, I didn't see you there either, sir.
Okay, lost a bit of HP here, it's okay.
See, that was smart what I just did.
I used the environment to my advantage.
Can I?
Yes, I can.
Oh my god, I couldn't move.
I was trying to jump, I think there was a pixel above me of dirt...
that didn't allow me to...
levitate.
That just fucked me up.
Uh oh, it's a big guy.
Good thing I have a big weapon.
I missed.
Okay, let me kill him.
Nice!
Yes, sir!
That's how we do it.
I will water myself a little bit, so I have more fire resistance.
Ah, there's so much gold, it's unfortunate.
Really want to grab it.
Ah, crap.
Is there a better way down?
How come I haven't found any wands yet?
That's kind of crazy.
What's going on here?
What's that?
Can I eat it?
Oh yeah!
I can eat the wax!
In fact...
We're going to add that to the list.
Hold on.
Where's this thing?
Here it is.
We're going to write...
Eat...
More...
Shrooms.
We've got to experiment with that.
Remember?
Very important.
All right.
Another portal.
Berserkium.
No, that's pheromone.
I'm going to get there.
I think pheromone could be very useful.
If you put it on enemies that are very powerful, they will essentially fight for you, right?
I mean, I haven't found...
It's like very impractical, I guess, because you have to put it in the bottle, then you have to find an enemy.
That will work for you, and you have to...
Oh, here we go.
Here's the roots.
So the roots are in the collapsed mines.
And here it is.
It's right to the west of collapsed...
It's actually right next to the roots.
So on my map, that would be sort of...
Let me see here.
It's like the dark area is like around here.
Right?
Let me just roughly draw that.
I don't even know... but I don't know what it looks like.
I'm just going to write dark area here for now.
It's freaking dark.
Like, if I go in here...
No, it's not going to reveal anything.
I need a light source.
Anything.
Or not anything, because even the all-seeing eye didn't fucking work.
The only thing that worked for me so far was the goddamn rock with the light on it.
Like, what?
So weird, isn't it?
You would think the all-seeing eye would see everything.
It would see all.
But it did, in fact, not see all.
It only saw some.
So it should be called some-seeing eye, in my opinion.
Because that is a lie.
What's going on up here?
Okay.
Kind of want to get up there.
Do I though?
66 HP.
We still have a bit of gas in the tank.
I'm stuck.
Yeah.
I think I can just enter from here, no?
Yes.
I hate these guys so much, because they bleed the bullshit.
Crit them.
Good.
Man, I'm out of water.
Damn, already.
Aw, no.
That should be enough.
Look at all the himises!
He jumped right up in my face.
That was a whole family I just murdered.
I shouldn't be hitting him, because now he bleeds lava.
It's a problem.
I don't have any water left, though.
Sick.
Why am I critting so much?
Actually, a good position I'm in.
Eh, sort of.
I got him.
Don't want to pick up the money, because there's too much lava.
Another portal?
Oh, that was so close.
That was pretty much lucky there.
Pure luck.
Another one.
Like, they're all next to each other, these portals.
I wonder if it's the same amount of portals every time.
Okay, so I need to find a way up there.
Blocked here.
Man, I haven't found a wand.
That means I hit that lamp.
Yeah, dead end here.
Hey, miss.
Here's the whiskey.
Ah, do I actually have to?
Ah, there we go, there we go.
I don't have to destroy it at all.
I'm drunk.
Heavy scent of booze, aiming is disturbed, and alcohol is flammable.
Nice.
It's going pretty good.
I should stop saying that, because inevitably it's going to go bad after I say it.
It's always like that.
Got some water at least.
Kind of want to go up here first.
In fact...
All right!
Dude, that's digging.
I like that, I like that.
I don't like that.
I don't like that either.
This is great!
Except I can't put it on the wand yet, but next time.
In the next holy mountain.
Why?
That was actually kind of lucky that he didn't jump on me there.
That was a prime target.
Come on, man.
Just... I need... Just one wand.
That's all I ask for.
I don't even want two, just one.
Oh no, everything's going to catch fire here.
Shit.
Did that guy die?
He did.
Oh, let me... Oh, what's this?
A circular.
Let me get the gold before it disappears.
Very good, very good.
Who else wants some?
Okay, so let's see here.
Now we are at the...
Wait, we're... Wait, are we at the end of...
No, no, no, there's still a lava.
Oh, wait a minute.
Where's the lava precisely here?
It's like a little...
Oh, wait a minute.
I need very precise...
areas here for my map.
I can't... Oh shit, I have to go around.
That's unfortunate.
I kind of want to grab some of that.
Wait a minute.
Slime potion?
Boo.
We don't want that.
Empty it over here.
This will be the slime area.
I think that berserkium can come in real handy.
Only get the berserk... Oh, wait, wrong bottle, wrong bottle.
Grab all the berserkium.
We're getting some water here as well, but that's fine.
That works.
Thank you.
That's a dead end here, but...
How do I get down there?
Probably from the left, right?
Here
we have the shop.
What the f... Oh, I didn't even see you.
What the hell?
You were camouflaged, my dude.
Well done, though.
Why do I back into the explosion every time?
Somehow I didn't lose any HP just now.
That's weird.
That was right in my face.
Come on, show me something.
A chest.
Some hearts.
Some...
What?
Once!
Oh, that was close.
Very close.
Hold on, what does berserkium actually do again?
I kind of forgot.
It increases crit chance, right?
But isn't that also what blood does?
That's why I'm asking, like, what is the actual difference there?
Berserk curse affects you.
No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I think it's making me do more damage.
I just did six... No, did I do six damage because I hit him twice?
I'm not sure.
Three damage, right?
But now, watch.
Just to confirm here.
Yeah, okay, double damage.
Wow!
Dude, Berserkium is insane, then.
I always thought it was crit.
The fuck?
Why did I come to that conclusion?
Double damage, man.
That is not bad.
I can't get up there.
Imagine accidentally falling into the portal because you run out of levitation power.
So far, we've done a pretty good job of exploring the hemisphere.
We can do better, though.
That would have been hard to dodge in these narrow corridors.
Ooh!
Now we're talking.
Okay, you know what?
That actually works in my favor.
Yeah, I'm happy with that.
Oh, I see you there.
I see you there, sir.
Hello?
We're sort of back at the top, right?
Almost.
Up first.
Remember, we already spent like 300 gold in the shop.
So, so far, we almost had 700 gold in the hemisphere, which is really not bad.
That's really nice.
Let me get that heart.
Now that all the fire is gone.
Okay, so this is the spot.
Tablet here, and then lava.
And what is above me?
Right here.
So, it sort of looks like...
Wait a minute.
Like, it doesn't go very high, right?
You have to go more left and then up.
Yeah, look.
Hold on.
So, that means we have to do...
Let's see here.
Hemisphere, right over here.
Let's remove this part here.
It's sort of...
Oh, so that means it's right below the pond.
It sort of goes up, right?
Like there, and then we have like a tablet there.
I'm gonna make it green.
There we go.
And then...
It makes a huge reservoir of lava, right?
I'm gonna make... I guess...
There we go.
Look at that shit.
Isn't that amazing?
So, it's actually... Oh, dude!
What if we...
What if we drain the water in the pond?
Make it fall into the... Oh, I guess we're just gonna create a crust on top of the lava.
Not gonna do much.
Okay.
Right.
Cool.
And then, over here, it's sort of...
It's like a cavern that goes up like that, I guess.
And this is the roof of that cavern, sort of.
It's a very...
Not precise drawing here, for sure, but...
Let me get rid of that.
I'll just let me get rid of that.
This is it for now.
It's gonna get better.
For sure.
Also, let me have a sip.
Cheers, everybody.
Oh, yeah!
I almost have no space on my desk, because I have the tablet I'm drawing on as well.
And I have two keyboards on here.
I can't get enough keyboards.
When I use a computer, I actually use two keyboards.
You may think I'm using a mouse here.
This is actually not a mouse.
I have my hand on another keyboard with the arrow keys, and that's how I control the mouse on a computer.
So the left hand, you know, standard WASD.
Right hand, I keep it on the right side of that keyboard for the mouse movement, so to speak.
It's very... Not a lot of people do that, but it's something I like to do.
Okay.
I'm gonna grab that, because why not?
I think I'm sort of done with the hemisphere.
It saddens me to say that, because we haven't found a single wand!
There's a guy in there, but I don't care about him.
It's actually unreal.
Like, what are the chances of that?
Let me go back to the collapsed mines real quick, just to see.
There's gotta be something.
Because the issue is, let's say we go to the Holy Mountain and we find amazing spells.
Well, great.
We can't use them, because we have shitty wands.
We have nowhere to put them, right?
We actually need wands.
Give me that water.
There we go.
Fall on that.
That is blood.
For some reason, I keep thinking that's lava, but it's not.
It's not lava.
What is burning?
Still.
Incredible.
Go here.
Yeah, I remember this spot.
Let's try to go further down here.
What's that?
Pheromone.
Okay, so that's the bottom here.
Man, this place is small as hell.
That means this doesn't go all the way to the top.
So on the map, the collapsed mines is actually just...
I guess the lower part of the size of the hemisphere.
Like half in height.
Approximately.
Because look, it sort of does like that.
Now it goes up here.
And above me right now, I wish I could zoom out a lot, you know, just to see everything around me.
But...
It is what it is.
Maybe there's a perk for that, you know?
You get to zoom out.
That would be a cool perk.
Alright, it's time to go, man.
We have no wands.
It is what it is.
Let's go through the portal.
We made the most of this place, for sure.
Like, it's not a bad start by any means, you know?
Where the hell am I going?
I just want to find the nearest portal.
I know I just came from one, but shouldn't there be one right over here?
Maybe not.
Oh, wait, there's this in here.
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
I can get in.
Watch.
Use the environment to my advantage.
Yes!
I keep forgetting I can do that!
I need to drench myself on water.
Now I can grab this.
I'm actually so resistant.
I should start doing this every time.
Oh, wait.
Oh, the portal is right there.
Okay.
There's someone to the right as well here.
I'm going to grab that.
It's for Sir Q.
All I want is to go down through a portal.
Here we go.
That's it.
Alright!
Hemisphere done!
Well, for now.
I could heal, but wait, let's not heal yet.
Okay.
Black Hole.
Chainsaw is good.
I love that.
And we have... Oh, is that...
Plasma Cutter!
Dude, we can dig like madmen!
But see, now we're missing wands, right?
Oh, stop opening that, please.
Oh, Peace with Gods is very intriguing.
But dude, is this what I think it is?
Fire immunity?
Hot damn!
Here's the thing.
I know this sounds dumb as hell, and this is what everyone says.
But theoretically, I can just not get hit by fire.
And I'll be fine, right?
This, however, is actually kind of big.
That's a big one.
I think I'm gonna go with that, it sounds crazy.
I know fire is my nemesis.
But I like this, especially because we found Black Hole.
So watch this.
I'm gonna get this.
We're gonna open up a path, because now we have peace.
Oh shit, tell me I can... tell me I can use it.
This is why we needed more wands!
Fuck!
Okay, you know what?
Oh, but now we can't... we can't exit now.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Yes, we can.
Plasma cutter.
Yes!
Okay, check it out.
We're gonna dig right here.
Right.
Dude, my heart just sank.
I should have been prepared for that message and that sound effect, of course, but I wasn't.
Just open it up slightly here.
I'm so scared of this plasma cutter.
Because I haven't hurt myself so much with this thing in the past.
I do definitely... I don't do... not have a license, I can't speak.
To wield this power tool here.
Scary stuff, that one.
I'm gonna grab that.
I will grab... what is this one again?
No, I don't like circle of stillness.
TNT?
Yes, that could be nice.
Luminous drill, that could be nice.
Electric torch.
Did I ever try that?
It's literally just... electric, isn't it?
Okay.
And this is sea of oil and glittering field, okay.
Rip black hole, but... maybe we can...
I definitely want plasma on this one.
Or that one, maybe, let's see.
No, no, I want it on this one, because here I can put two.
And if I put this here... and I put... this is gonna make it shoot faster.
Well, very slightly, I guess.
Yeah, it's not that great.
Reduces recharge time?
Ayy, there we go!
Hell yeah!
That's great!
Wow!
Okay.
That's a solid wand!
I like it!
I really do!
That's a good start!
Alright, let's go!
Let's find some wands, we come back here, and we...
Oh, wait, I have to heal.
Oh, should I heal, though?
Yes, I should, yes, I should.
Yes, I should.
Don't be an idiot.
Go back and heal, dummy.
You will regret it later if you don't.
Yep, 185 HP, actually insane at this point.
Like, the only issue is the mana, but that's fine.
I mean, this is definitely the best I can do right now, I think.
Okay, here we go.
It's time for the cold pits.
Oh, cold pits, I have arrived.
I have a mission to uncover the secrets of this land.
Uh-oh.
Oh my god, oh my god, it's toxic everywhere!
Entire level is filled with this now.
Oh god, this thing's gonna blow, isn't it?
Oh, no.
Ah, no.
Look at what I've done.
Get plenty of water.
We're gonna need it.
There we are.
Whoa.
I see you there.
Oops.
Yo, watch this, watch this.
It's not exactly what I intended, but it worked.
I was just gonna kick off the top rock and let it fall on him.
But that works just fine as well.
We've got some shaking here.
Whoa.
Something's blowing up somewhere.
Watch, nothing stops me.
Oh, it's so...
It's a scary tool, but god damn have I missed you.
I have access to absolutely everything now.
Now I wonder if there is gold.
Like there.
Will that just disintegrate the gold?
I'm not actually sure what just happened.
Let me test.
Oh, wait.
The gold is just gone, isn't it?
Dang.
Here we go.
Finally a wand.
And it's not terrible.
This is pretty good.
Yo, wait a minute.
I'm going back.
Because I'm putting that first combination into that wand instead.
It's going to make it shoot for longer.
And it's just going to feel better.
Didn't mean to fall all the way down.
Yeah.
See?
Peace with the gods?
Amazing.
I love peace with the gods.
I don't want to anger the gods, dude.
That's terrible.
Wait a minute.
Firebomb is...
limitless?
What the hell?
Wait.
That is not bad.
I mean, neither is this.
Oh, wait.
I was confusing it with that.
Look how similar they look.
Firebomb and firebolt.
Yeah.
I could also...
No, I don't know why.
Fuck Poland.
I like this, I think.
Let's try and rock that.
It's a little bit slow.
But, you know, it is what it is.
Here I can do this, I guess.
How about we do TNT here?
TNT with...
Yeah, that's pretty much just TNT.
And then put this one on the number one.
Number two is digging.
Well, they're both digging, I guess.
But yeah, here we go.
Number three is that one, okay.
Let's not forget it.
Number three is plasma.
Three is plasma.
Oh, what's this?
An impenetrable wall?
Not for me.
Let me be careful here where I stand.
Come on, one more.
Yes!
Oh, what the fuck is that?
Yo, what the hell?
Wait, what?
It's me!
Uh...
What?
That's me!
Uh, sir?
You like that?
What the hell is that?
It's a ghost version.
Oh, yeah, that was a sweet hit.
Come here.
You know, now I actually kind of like the slow-moving projectiles.
I can sort of shoot them and bait them around the corner.
Oh!
Oh my god, I'm on fire!
It's a duel!
I hit him a little bit there.
He has HP, what the hell?
Oh my god, there's so much fire.
Where are you?
Dude, I'm scared of that wand he has.
That looks like it's gonna do some damage to me!
What the?
I...
Can he die?
Oh!
Oh my god, oh my god!
Holy shit!
This is no joke, this is no joke.
What the hell?
He's taking no damage from this.
Let me try TNT.
I
can't hit anything.
Where'd he go?
Where'd you go?
Sir?
There you are.
Oh my god, that...
It's scary when the enemies have wands, man!
Is he coming here?
Yes, he is.
I'm hitting him for nothing.
Oh, that hit him for a lot.
Okay, dynamite it is.
Yeah, that's it.
Now we're cooking with diesel.
Oh my god!
Gold!
Grab the other one.
There we go!
Oh!
I mean, it's kind of shit, but...
and it's shuffle too.
I'll take it though.
It's nice.
I like this one.
Chain Bolt.
Pretty neat.
Lost a lot of HP to that though.
What a crazy enemy.
I have never seen that guy.
Ever.
Aha!
More HP for moi.
I do dig it.
Okay, so look at this.
It actually digs.
Oh my god!
We're going to be digging so much.
Look how easy it is!
Oh well, okay, I guess gray rock is still kind of hard to get through.
But you know, it's really good still.
Like coal like this?
Mmm, just easy.
I'm feeling good about this run.
I should stop jinxing things.
I really should.
But I am feeling good.
I did lose a lot of HP.
I'm at half HP.
I warned for me.
Fuck yeah, dude!
There it is!
Teleport achieved!
In fact, I kind of like it more than this.
I mean, this is nice.
I already have a double.
Chain Bolt is kind of meh now that I have that.
Right?
Although, Triple Kit could be nice.
Umm...
Kind of want to go back with both of these wands.
Let me go back with this one first.
Oh, I'm right here!
Okay, perfect, perfect.
Easy peasy, lemon squeezy.
Oh wait, I can just use it.
Oh, it's instant.
So now, I just want...
One of these, I guess.
The rest can sort of fuck off.
There we go.
Now I go exchange the wand.
Peace with gods!
Feels amazing.
Here it is.
Hold on, I see that gold right there.
I need to get it.
It's so much gold as well, look!
It's like... oh shit, oh shit.
I gotta be careful with that.
Here we go.
Unfortunately, it's a shuffle wand, but I only care about the spells.
I want this, that, and that.
Wand can, I guess, stay in my inventory for now.
Oh, the question is, would I like some of these things here?
I don't think I do.
Teleport, obviously.
Maybe this will be on teleport now.
Yes!
Or, wait a minute, 85, 11.
Oh, dude, way better plasma wand.
This one can go away, I guess.
There we go.
That's it, that's how I like it.
In fact, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Maybe this is better.
That is pretty sweet.
It's just a little bit inaccurate, that's all.
You know, it does 5 damage per pop.
This one, though, shoots so quick that when I hit something, it's just a lot of poof.
And it also digs, but so does this.
I do like this more.
Yeah, also because I haven't done this before.
This is my first time trying that sort of thing.
I'm just scared about the fire when I do this, you know?
I can set myself on fire.
There's a chest in there!
Holy shit, I need to keep an eye out here, man.
A wand!
Yo!
Not bad!
I'll go deposit that as well.
Everything gets deposited.
Back to the vault.
Yes.
I don't think I like Poland.
I don't like Firebolt.
I don't like Electric Torch.
What else do I not like?
Maybe I don't like...
No, I like the rest, I think.
Burning Trail?
Wait, what's the difference between that and this one?
What is this one called?
Fire Trail!
But...
How is that different?
160, 46...
I will...
In fact, wait a minute.
I'll put it back to this.
That's good.
Now, the fourth wand can be...
It's shuffle, so for now...
No, you know what?
I'm gonna keep it empty.
Definitely.
Otherwise, I'd have to come back here later and deposit the spells I put in it now.
And I don't want to do that.
Nope.
No, sir.
Let's really try and keep an eye out now.
Some of these chests are just hidden right in plain sight almost, and I missed it.
So there's something in there as well.
Let's dig.
With our amazing plasma thingy, of course.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, we got one of those.
Wait, what's this?
Wait a minute.
What if I light these candles?
Will something happen?
Let me try and light them.
Oh, I destroyed them.
Whoops.
Okay, I've been up there.
Let me go down here.
Aha!
Oh, they dissolve in water, of course.
Whoop.
Okay.
How do I do this, then?
Hmm.
I don't like it.
And you know why I don't like it?
I'll tell you why I don't like it.
Hold on, I can show you in a second why I don't like it.
I need to get into safety, though.
I'll show you.
Watch this.
Look at that.
You know what that is?
That's 100% a Dark Souls mimic.
And I think I somehow have killed one of them without noticing.
Why would it be in here, right?
That's why I shoot everything.
But I can't really get to it.
So I don't know what to do about that right now.
Uh...
I guess I'll leave it for now.
There's a wand there.
Hello!
Okay, you know what?
This wand I have here, I'm actually not the happiest about it because it will set me on fire.
Oh!
Maybe I do like the normal projectiles better, you know?
It does do a lot of damage, can't deny that.
What are that?
Let's see.
Energy orb.
Earthquake shot!
Yo, I like that a lot!
I love me some earthquake.
That was so much fun the last time.
We're gonna do that here.
Watch.
Boink!
Oh, it didn't even...
Ha ha!
Look how everything is earthquaking.
In fact, that's just saying, look how everything is quaking, I should say.
And that was a shuffle one, wasn't it?
It was, okay.
So that's why it didn't quake the first time around.
Whoa!
Hello!
This is doing some sick damage.
It really is.
Imagine having this wand with the fire immunity.
Huh?
Unfortunately, I chose peace with the gods instead and I think it was wise.
Fire is dangerous, yes.
But the gods scare me.
They really do.
What the fuck?
They shavoo here.
Let's quake it.
Oh!
Holy shit, that just blew up.
Shit!
How did I just catch fire?
What?
Did I just catch fire from shooting my...
Just shooting my bullets?
Weird.
100 HP.
101 HP actually.
Nice.
I'm playing well.
Water him.
So he may become a flower one day.
Oh, I'm gonna get through here.
Oh, that dig's so good.
Such a good dig right there.
Pfft!
I like
that even more!
Fuck yeah!
Can I even shoot it too?
Wait a minute.
I can't.
God damn it.
But I... there's a wand here actually.
No, don't drain that.
Yo, this is the best plasma cutter I've ever had.
Uh oh.
Get plasma!
What do we got?
Uh, energy or saw blade orbit?
That one is scary AF.
I don't like any of these.
Nope.
I hate it.
In fact, I hate it.
That thing is scary?
Whoa!
Jesus!
Okay, that guy has the same shield I had last time.
How do I deal with him?
Oh wait, he can't get through?
Watch this.
You like plasma, boy?
Yeah!
Yes, sir!
That's how you do it.
Oh wait, oh wait, where am I now?
Is it time to get high?
Get some water here.
In fact, get all the water here.
Mix it.
Let's go over here.
Oh, load all that water.
Oh yeah, I'm sucking it all up.
I don't want to release the water.
Release the water!
That guy was teleporting.
Does that mean he hit some teleporting liquid?
I think that's what he means.
This place is known for that, right?
I'm scared.
Maybe it's time to get the fuck out, huh?
Oh, but wait a minute.
Is it though?
Is it time?
Or should we just... just a little bit exploring?
Just a tad amount.
Small amount.
Hello.
Oh.
No, no, no, no, no.
How did that not die?
Hey!
Sir?
Plasma cutter is actually kind of amazing at killing enemies too.
So we have 1,400 monies, boys.
I think we gotta go.
I think it's time to go.
We gotta go.
Unless...
I kind of want to find a better wand before we go.
Let's just explore a little bit more.
Probably...
Let me get up there.
Hello, hello.
I hate these guys.
I have the worst weapon against this, by the way.
Yeah, I don't want to go that way.
Let's stay in the coal pits for now.
Look at that guy!
He's gonna have a bad day now.
He got blown up a million times.
And it was glorious.
Where'd you come from?
Fell from the sky.
I see you up there.
A wand!
Shit.
Shuffle again.
God damn it.
I hate the shuffle.
Every wand is a shuffle wand.
Oh no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Not these guys.
Please.
Oh no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, yeah, it's so bad.
It's so bad.
The way it jumps around!
There's lava and stuff.
We gotta be careful here.
That's a wand!
Okay.
How do I...
Let's do this.
Wait, is the plasma stopped by water?
Is that what I'm seeing here?
I think it is.
Oh, okay.
Interesting.
Let's see.
Thousand and f...
Oh, this is a shitty wand as well.
Firebolt with trigger though.
Hmm.
No.
No thanks.
All this is gonna explode now.
This is the issue with the fire.
Hello, hello, hello, hello, sir.
I wanna get in there.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I can shoot fireballs too, boys.
That's right.
Mine's are better than yours.
You hurt me.
Play it safe.
I see lava on the floor.
Okay.
Another wand.
Good.
All I'm looking for...
Oh my god.
All I'm looking for right now is a decent wand.
So I can make a decent wand.
Pretty much.
It sounds simple, doesn't it?
But things ain't that simple in this game.
Now what do we got?
Now that's maybe what I'm talking about.
I mean...
No, it's not.
Never mind.
I'm tempted to just leave.
We have very low HP.
Uh, wait a minute.
Okay, the wand I'm holding right now, I think it's a...
It always has like a fire effect on it.
Similar to how electricity wands have the electricity.
So if I go in that oil, I'm fucked.
Unless I switch wands.
I just wanna quickly see what's over here.
Before I move on.
Just quick.
Just really quick.
Look how that reaction just...
And look, look, look how slow it is?
Watch.
I disturb the surface.
And it mixes.
Amazing.
Grab the water.
I don't know why I'm so impressed by this mechanic.
It's just mind-blowing.
I think I was here.
1600 gold, dude.
We get to re-roll a lot.
Where are you?
There you are.
Ah, you should die, right?
There we go.
What does it say?
Portal deeper.
Huh, I never noticed it said that.
Deeper indeed.
Look how good that is at digging through coal.
What?
There's a wand?
Are you kidding me?
I just dug straight to a wand.
Hello?
What is that?
Uh...
That, ooh.
Zero cast delay?
Wait.
Reach up, hmm.
Do I want, no.
Do I want this?
120 mana max is not a lot.
Only capacity of two?
Mmm...
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
I don't know.
Probably not.
Oh, hello.
What's up, man?
Are you gonna...
Stay there?
Wait, wait, yeah, yeah!
Oh!
He has the wand!
Oh no, I could die here.
Go in!
No, we don't take any risks.
Is he gonna come through the portal?
I've had that happen before.
Come on.
Alright, fine.
Doesn't look like it.
Let's see!
Uh, what's this?
Delayed spell cast.
Right.
Wait, what the hell's that?
Circle of transmogrification.
I guess everything gets transmogrified inside of it?
Circle of fire, what's that?
Odd fire bolt.
Huh.
Let's see the perks.
Summon acidikivi.
You gain an artifact that allows you to call this celestial rage.
That sounds badass.
Cordyceps?
I've seen that a bunch.
No more knockback.
I don't like these very much.
I mean, this one...
Like, what if my...
What if the celestial rage dies or whatever?
I guess it's sort of a...
It's another follower I can get, right?
If he dies, that's the end of that perk.
You know?
I want to reroll.
Slime blood.
Stainless armor is good.
Huh?
Why?
What happened?
I didn't do anything.
Someone else did something.
Good thing I have the perk, huh?
Good thing I have the perk.
I think I want this.
It's crazy, I've had that perk the last three or four runs I've done.
Like, it's just always there.
And look at this.
Look how many perks there are over here.
There's so many I haven't even found yet, and it keeps giving me stainless armor.
Come on, man.
Give me something new.
Reduce spread.
Now, that one is pretty good.
I like that.
Oh, I have no more space.
Gotcha.
Um...
Get rid of maybe one of these.
Yikes.
Let's see what we can make here, huh?
Let me put black holes here for now.
Just stack them there.
This is the black hole stack.
All of them go here.
Boink.
That way I can just grab any black hole whenever I want to.
I have a speed up.
And...
Oh, wait, we have a light now.
That's actually good.
For the dark area?
When we come back later?
Oh, because we are coming back later.
Let's see here.
This is a no shuffle.
This is the wand I want to do something with.
Let's see what we can make.
We have a chainsaw, so we can make things go fast.
We also have that.
And that.
This is actually really nice.
It's not going to be an amazing wand, because it's going to recharge quite slowly.
Alright.
But...
Let's have that one.
Let's have this.
And...
Or...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is good, this is good.
I definitely want a...
Let's do a triple, huh?
So we affect reduce spread on everything.
Do we have any other modifiers?
This one.
How much mana does that cost?
Three, that's nothing.
Fuck it.
Let's see how fast this is now.
Oh, wait a minute.
Yo!
Having this completely eliminates the spread?
Look at that!
Oh, never mind.
I'm an idiot.
I can't believe I forgot about that one.
I thought because...
Oh, it's moving fast.
It doesn't have time to spread out too much, you know?
But maybe that does help a little bit with the spread.
The fact that it's faster flying, you know?
I'm not sure.
Maybe.
Triple there.
And let's go...
How about this?
What does that look like?
Let's check the damage on this.
It's kind of... bad.
Also, let me see the board.
It's just shooting all of that.
It's actually not what I'm looking for.
I'm looking for...
One, two...
Like that?
Man.
The chainsaw is...
If you put it in the right spot, everything just sort of happens.
But...
I'm not...
I never quite understood...
why that works and why it doesn't sometimes.
It's a bit odd.
This one does add...
some castor lay.
Why don't I just go nuts and only use spark bolts?
They're kind of fast, right?
Okay.
Oh, but then they're all going to bounce off of each other.
I don't like that.
Don't like that at all.
I do like this idea here.
Let's try this.
Modifier.
Reduce spread.
Triplicate.
And that's it.
Let's see how fast this is.
That's not terrible.
Increase speed on it, too.
Oh, wait.
That is definitely...
Never mind.
Oh, I like the speed a lot.
The speed is great.
Speed is good.
Let me chainsaw that.
Shoots faster.
Shoots faster?
Yep.
Yep, yep, yep.
I can also...
If I...
The thing I'm trying to do...
See that right there.
Shoots that.
But then it shoots...
The entire thing again.
Because it shoots this one.
But what does this do when it collides with something?
It shoots the next spell.
And the next spell is actually...
That one.
And that spell has all these three modifiers.
That's why it's showing this first.
And then...
All these again.
You see that?
So, mana goes out quick with this.
Maybe that's not the best.
Chain bolt could be cool, but it costs a lot of mana.
I think I kind of like this.
But I also don't really like it.
Can I reduce...
I could reduce recharge some more with this, I guess.
Oh yeah, I run out of mana quick.
Mana is actually the issue here.
That cost 30 mana!
Jesus.
Hmm...
Maybe I don't like it then.
Should I just go for a simple...
I don't know, man.
Plasma for sure, right?
This is good.
I feel like this is a solid wand.
On that one, let's just have this.
With the speed up, that could be cool.
We probably don't need that in that case.
Is that actually any faster?
I can't really tell.
I don't think that affects it at all.
Weirdly enough.
Huh.
That's kind of disappointing.
Hmm...
What else should I do?
I kind of just want to come back with a better wand and experiment when I have a better wand.
This wand sucks.
That's the plan.
We go out there and we come back with a better wand.
Yep.
Wait a minute.
Concentrated light.
Uh...
Kind of want to try that real quick.
Concentrated.
Let me get rid of that one.
Is that the one that hurts me?
Let me see what it does.
It bounces.
Pinpointed beam of light does 10 damage.
What if we put it here?
I go oomph quick.
That is...
pretty cool.
Honestly.
Wow, the difference.
I think I'll try that.
Let's go with that.
Yeah.
Let's rock that for a bit.
We can always come back here, I guess.
On this wand, I will actually put some...
No, grab that.
Throw away this and that.
Ah, no, it doesn't have mana for that.
This one does, though.
But then this is a shitty wand, isn't it?
Yeah, it runs out quick.
Nah, I'm going to save these black holes, I guess.
Save them!
This comes with me.
I can replace it.
Yes.
Let's go.
Oh, we got to heal, we got to heal.
Let's not be dumb.
You know what I want to find?
Another healing wand.
Like the one I had in the last good run I had.
Because I finally figured out how to heal myself with it.
But then I squandered everything.
Why do I keep getting scared by that?
Sometimes I hate my fucking body.
It just has the weirdest reactions to noises.
Oh my god.
This is going to go oom fast, by the way.
It's going to be precise.
That's neat.
That is neat.
These guys can fuck right off.
I hate them.
With a passion.
I got to be careful, though.
If there's a lot of enemies, I'm fucked.
That is my weakness here.
Weakness is a lot of enemies.
A couple I can handle.
Okay.
Oh, I hear someone.
I hear a sniper, I think.
Let me...
Try to dig through here.
Where's the sniper?
I see you there.
Man, it shoots exactly where your cursor is.
That's the best thing about this wand.
Like, it may not be great at a lot of things, but it's great at that, you know?
Hell yeah.
I also think it does more damage than it's showing.
Because those guys have a lot of HP, right?
And he just died immediately.
Let's see here, actually.
This wand has 370 mana max.
This costs 30, right?
So that's pretty much 10 shots in a matter of one second, basically.
Whoa!
The concentrated light reduces castellae.
What?
And by quite a lot as well.
Also, it has a damage explosion on it, too.
Didn't even realize.
Cool.
Like, it only shows 30 damage, but it's way more than 30.
It is at least 100.
This wand is sick!
I'm using a lot of my water on this, but that's fine.
Whoa, wait, that bigs!
Uh, slightly, I guess.
Dude, just pressing the mouse button once almost empties my mana.
If you wanted to try to shoot just one spell, you can't.
Not with this wand.
Oh, that guy didn't die.
Drain it.
Yeah, look, water stops the plasma.
A snowman!
What do we got?
A shovel wand, of course, like always?
I don't like this.
That is not a good wand for me.
I am unhappy with this wand.
You know, you could use this to evaporate water.
Quite effectively.
Oh!
I hurt myself with this somehow.
Wait, did I actually hit something in the back there on accident?
Concentrated mana.
That could come in handy.
Actually, let's test it!
Oh yeah, it totally recharges way quicker, okay.
I was kind of hoping it would just recharge so quick that I could just hold down the button on this.
But it's gonna be good if there's a lot going on.
Aha!
My rock!
I'm gonna... I think I'm gonna get it.
Just in case I find infinite spells.
You know?
That rock right there is... something else.
I have a whole new relationship with that rock after that one run we had.
Get rid of that last piece, please.
There we go.
Wow, it doesn't kill it, okay.
Oh man!
You bastard!
Okay, this is some bullshit.
Oh my god!
There we go.
I have to abuse the fact that his tracking is really bad.
That guy is scaring me.
Drink the concentrated mana?
Where did he go?
Where did you go?
Where are you?
Oh, you're down there somewhere.
Freaking havoc!
Multiple!
Good thing it's not the electricity, dude.
Oh wait,
they probably hate fire, right?
Oh wait, I don't have fire on me.
Shit.
Got him!
Well, one of them.
How about plasma?
You like that?
Actually, he hates it.
Nice!
Yay!
Success!
That's oil...
and ice.
Hello!
I can also snipe!
Oh, this is scary.
This is actually a scary situation I'm in.
There's way too many!
This is my weakness, when there's so many enemies.
Then I can't do shit.
Whoa!
Nah, we gotta get the fuck out.
Oh no.
I keep forgetting, I have a teleport wand.
Use the teleport wand!
It is a small teleport.
Maybe I even prefer that over the long one.
Just because sometimes with the long one, you may appear in a place you don't expect.
Whereas with the small one, there's always a guarantee you can't go any further than X distance.
You know what?
These things right here?
They kind of look like those we found in the ocean.
Under the hut.
Those container thingies.
That works.
Doink!
Plasma cutter.
Once again.
Comes to the rescue.
Uh oh.
You didn't die from that, I know that.
Wait, what?
Oh!
You got turned into a sheep, is that?
It's polymorphine.
I guess he fell in.
Oh, hello.
Uh oh.
Ah, nice.
Get rid of the water!
Nice!
What do we got up here?
I also have to add to the map that this area connects up to the hemisphere.
In fact, that's to the right of the lava lake.
Everything sort of makes sense.
I'm scared of that thing, I'm scared of that thing.
Do not explode on me.
There's a guy in there.
Let's chill for a second.
1700 gold.
Don't you snipe me.
What is that?
Whoa!
There was another one.
Just look at where...
Wait a minute!
We need to fill this with some kind of liquid.
100%.
I just wonder what it is.
Shit.
What does it say?
Upside down triangle.
Red orbs.
Water.
Wait.
Two...
Three.
Maybe just... because there's already water in here, maybe just fill it up the rest.
We gotta find more water.
Shit.
Water, water, water.
Actually, hold on.
There's bubbles in the water.
Could that mean it's something with bubbles in it?
Whatever that... sparkling water.
Oh, come on, man.
Oh my god!
This guy's killing me!
I think it may be time for us to leave.
36 HP.
I don't want to take chances...
Oh, there's actually water right below me here.
You know what?
I'm gonna grab that water.
Since we're here and the water's right there, we gotta try it.
I think that will kill me down here.
Hopefully not.
Give me all the water.
There we go.
Come on.
Maybe I fill it up to the line where the waves are.
Okay!
Yo, that's a sick one!
Piercing shot.
Makes the projectile fly through enemies but harmful to the cast and now that's scary.
Wait, damage minus 15.
Hmm.
What?
That's not good.
Minus 15 though?
That's a lot!
Oh man, do I say goodbye to my rocks?
Yes, I do.
No question!
A somewhat peculiar bouncy explosive bolt.
I don't think I should shoot that.
Nope.
Okay, fill up this thing again.
That was great, man.
Now I'm gonna go back up, actually, to the holy mountain.
And we're gonna do some experimenting with this new wand here.
Also, let's be careful.
Let me drink that.
Just a bit of the...
Just a bit of the good stuff.
So I'm ready.
Okay, we're actually right here.
Nice!
Beautiful!
Okay, let's see how good this wand is, huh?
If I... just as a test here, if I put these here...
Yes!
It's already amazing!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
We can... we can... okay, hold on.
That cost 30 mana though.
That's... it's kind of a lot.
Hmm.
Let me see this.
So that's pretty nice.
Let's see how much damage it does.
I'm gonna test on the other statue.
Because I somehow... not somehow, I definitely did destroy the first one completely.
Wait, what?
Maybe I can't see the damage anymore after I've left?
Wait, what the...
Oh, wait!
Minus 15 damage?
Oh, no!
Is that what's happening?
Bro, this is useless.
Are you kidding me?
What kind of a shit wand is this?
Minus 15 damage is...
Fuck!
It's useless.
God damn it.
I thought I found something great and I solved the puzzle and everything.
But you know what?
Maybe I can put something on here that doesn't need damage anyway.
You know?
Something like... you guessed it.
It's a black hole!
Oh, yeah!
Why did I just get a weird effect on me?
Did I just eat a black hole?
What just happened?
I just ate something.
Okay, I like this.
Do I need to buy anything else before I leave?
That's the question.
You know what?
Water trail?
Kind of like that.
Maybe delayed spell cast could be cool down the road?
Or whatever, you know?
How about we get rid of...
Um...
I don't even know.
Maybe that one.
No.
Wait a minute.
One of these.
I don't need to keep all of them.
There we go.
What is this?
Circle of fire?
No.
I don't think I want circle of transmogrification either.
I am good the way I am.
That's just the way I am.
Alright, let's find a portal.
And we get out.
We take no chances now.
I do wonder though, with that thing I filled with water...
If I had filled it with a more... expensive liquid.
Let's say berserkium all the way up.
Maybe it would have given me an even better wand.
You know, maybe the quality of the wand...
is determined by...
the rarity of the liquid you put in.
Oh, I hear it.
Yep, I hear you.
I hear you.
Oh shit, don't you hit me.
Let's not go that way.
It's gotta be a better way down.
Place I've already been maybe.
Shit.
Whoa, yeah, let's not go that way either.
Man, where... hmm...
I gotta go down somewhere.
In fact, I don't think I found a portal in this place yet, so...
Oh, he died.
Oh.
Oh no.
Where are you?
Oh no!
Oh shit!
Get him!
Oh!
Fuck me!
Take it.
Heal up immediately.
Holy crap.
Alright, fine, finally we hit wands.
Jesus!
Would you look at that?
There's all kinds of shit here.
Oh my god, okay.
Alright.
Let's see the perks.
Uh, electric...
electricity immunity.
Explo- ooh!
Brother!
What's this?
Extra item in Holy Mountain.
No, I don't like that.
Dude, I...
I gotta go with...
I gotta go with explosion immunity.
How is that not an immediate thing to go for when you find it?
Uh, okay, let's see here.
I think I definitely want to buy this wand.
Let's put this wand on the floor.
Boink!
Take this.
Let's see here.
360 mana.
Minus 0.12 cast delay.
You know what?
I think I just understood why that's even a thing.
So basically it is a 0 cast delay.
But, it gives you a little headroom.
In case you add spells that add cast delay.
That's pretty much all that does.
I can't believe I didn't think about that earlier.
That has to be what is happening.
19 capacity, that's wild.
What is it that it always casts?
Uh, wait a minute, let me see it here.
How do I see it?
Makes a projectile more destructive to the environment.
You know what?
That's perfect for me.
I'm immune to that shit.
Yeah!
Fuck yeah.
Look at that.
Accelerative homing.
And another reduced recharge.
Triples and formation stuff.
Let me put this in the water.
I don't want these.
Uh, I don't want that either.
Don't want that either.
Don't want that I don't think.
The rest I kind of want.
But I want them over here, on the floor.
Put them there.
This one I want to keep.
Let's put this one here.
This one I also want to keep.
Let's put that one there.
There we go.
Let's see what we can do now.
So, mana charge speed is decent.
The only problem here is the recharge time.
So if we can reduce that in some way.
With what we've got.
Let's see the other ones real quick.
Maybe they have something for that.
I'm not sure they...
I think this one does.
Reduce recharge.
But, it also makes it spread in every direction, right?
So, unless you put it at the end.
Where it doesn't affect a projectile.
It's a modifier.
It's still going to give the bonus.
You know what?
Yes.
Actually, that's genius.
Put this wand back on the floor.
Right?
So if I were to do this.
But it shoots super slow because recharge time is high here, right?
Wow, is that actually...
Look at the explosion on that.
Lovely.
Alright.
Let's add another one of these.
Hello?
Hell yeah.
Already much better.
But if I do this now.
Right.
It's still going to sort of shoot everywhere, I guess.
No, actually it is sort of...
Oh, the mana is the problem now.
Dude, but dude, what if we do this?
That is an explosive spark bolt there.
If I add this...
Hmm, I want it faster.
It's not fast enough.
Why is that not fast enough?
Let's see here.
0.88 recharge.
So, cast-a-lay is definitely not the issue, right?
No, no, no.
These both reduce by 0.66.
So I have 0.22 left.
And this is subtracting 0.25.
That is...
Let me remove that.
Maybe that's fucking it up.
Why is that so slow?
Hold on.
Can I...
Yeah, I can definitely stack these, right?
Let's do a quick test.
So, with nothing on it...
0.88 seconds in between.
Right?
That's the thing we have here.
Now we reduce it by 0.33 seconds.
Using this one.
Faster.
Then we stack it with this.
Even faster.
So we're still limited by recharge.
And the reason I know that is because we see the same...
No, wait, never mind.
Yeah, yeah, we see the...
It's just shooting this off, right?
And then it starts over.
So if I add...
Where's that thing I had?
This one?
Here.
Then...
Oh, but if I add it first...
Then it shoots super fast, right?
But it shoots it randomly.
But by adding it at the end...
Wait, is that actually changing?
No, it doesn't actually affect anything.
Yeah, okay.
Unfortunate.
But if I add the chainsaw...
No, that only reduces recharge time.
That's actually cool.
That's what I want.
So why don't I put this here instead?
So I'm just curious why this is not like...
Machine gunning, basically.
Why is it not machine gunning?
Because I have definitely reduced this...
0.88 down to zero.
By now.
Surely.
0.17, like 0.66...
Plus 0.17, that's like...
What is that?
0.73 plus 0.83...
Almost.
Right?
I mean, mana is still kind of an issue, I guess.
So I guess if I were to machine gun, it still wouldn't be great.
That is interesting.
Yeah, so I basically don't like it.
What if I add a double?
And I do...
Um, this one?
No.
Maybe I add...
Yeah, that's fine.
Change, please.
There we fucking go, baby!
Hold on, let's see, let's try and understand what's happening.
Why is that suddenly machine gunning?
Out of fire!
Okay.
Okay, so the explosion does put me on fire.
Good to know, good to know.
Hold on.
Why is that machine gunning?
I cast...
double.
That one, and that.
And this one is going to cast another spell when it collides with something.
What is that other spell?
It's the next spell, and the next spell is...
the double spell.
Right?
So...
Wait, is it actually...
I'm not seeing on the board what I'm expecting to see here.
Let's say I remove this.
Whoa!
Okay, it's still super quick.
If I now put in... let's say this one.
It's still amazingly quick.
And very destructive, I guess.
Because of all the explosions.
Not bad.
If we reduce spread on that as well.
Sweet!
And then we accelerate the projectile.
Brother!
Oh!
Hell yeah!
Now that's what I'm talking about.
Look at that shit.
That's some good damage right there.
Not bad at all.
Let's try with this.
Phew!
Mana goes out quick with that, though.
Because it costs a lot to cast.
Let's see how much mana it goes with that one.
I mean, it's not as much damage, and I run Oom quick.
I think the best is definitely that one, no?
You can shoot for a long time.
If only I had an add mana.
That would be...
Insano style right now.
That would be the cherry on top.
But we can go look for that.
That's no problem.
That's fine.
Umm...
Black holes?
Should I be black holing?
Why not?
Why don't we black hole a little bit?
Wait, where are my black holes?
Did I...
Did I forget to take them with me?
Oh shit!
Did I actually forget them?
I could buy this as well.
You know what?
Buy this.
I want that one.
I want...
That one?
Sure, give me that one.
It's two.
And then we switch it back.
Because...
So it casts five spells in a pentagonal pattern.
No.
That one though.
Twenty mana drain.
Let's see the damage on that.
Oh, it runs out really quick.
I like this best.
I like that best.
That's solid.
That is solid.
That's gonna be my main damage dealer.
Then we have teleport, then we have plasma cutter.
Very nice.
I could add a delayed spell cast to this to make it super safe, but it's a shuffle, so never mind.
I was kidding.
We're not doing that.
Ha ha ha.
Funny.
Okay.
Are we about ready to go?
Wait.
Ah!
Here are my black holes.
Umm...
Point sevens.
Yeah.
Gimme, gimme that back.
In fact, do this.
Take that there.
Take this here.
There we go!
Let's rock and roll, baby.
In fact, I am gonna be stylish and use the black hole on my way out.
No, I'm not.
Look the other way!
Leave me alone.
I hate that, that...
Why does it have to pop up and be so scary when they're just telling me it's okay?
You know?
It's like, you go into a restaurant and you start pissing on the floor and the manager comes over and says...
Hey, you're allowed to do that!
Have a good day, sir.
And then he walks off again, you know?
Yeah, okay, okay, but...
Don't say it like that.
And that voice...
Can I...
Here we go, boys!
We are in the Heezy base.
Fuck yeah.
Actually pretty nice for the first run today, to get here.
But...
Let's test this bad boy.
Oh!
Oh, I like.
Me likey.
Oh, me likey a lot.
Those guys don't die instantly, that's unfortunate.
Oh my goodness gracious.
Good thing I'm explosion immune, huh, in this place?
Hahaha.
Oh, it's digging so good!
Yo!
The explosiveness on this one, like the always casts, is actually nuts.
Doesn't dig through steel though, but that's to be expected, I guess.
Why is that shaking so much?
Shaking intensifies.
Does this give me...
It...
Oh my god.
I was about to say, does it have some recoil, but it does.
Why did I not just hold down the button?
I just let him shoot me for 30 damage.
That was really dumb.
Okay, we're good on water.
Kinda wish I had found a broken wand, you know?
That's right, you like that?
Come here, you.
Oh, I'm actually stuck.
Whoa.
The damage is not phenomenal on this.
That's the one thing.
You know, the fact that I can't one-shot these guys reduces my chance of survival drastically.
Because it just gives them yet another opportunity to kill me every time I don't kill them, you know?
It's actually such a huge deal.
Still not dead, it's incredible.
No, he died, he died, okay.
That's something.
Fucking hell.
169 HP, let's take it easy.
That thing's gonna blow as well, let me get the hell out of here.
Even though I'm explosion immune, I'm not fire immune.
Man, if I had taken fire immunity, I could have been explosion and fire immune.
But, I'm still happy I didn't.
Just because of the gods.
Fucking hell.
The recoil pushed me into the fire there.
That thing's gonna blow.
Let's blow it up.
Watch this.
Slithering path.
Makes the projectile move rapidly in a slithering manner like a snake.
And it adds projectile speed.
That is actually not a bad wand.
490 mana max, 149 charge.
Huh.
That's a decent, right there.
It's better than this wand.
No, wait, is it?
No, it's not.
It is.
Because this one has that and that sucks.
But, no.
So the question is, should I be using something else against these guys?
Probably not.
Okay.
What is my mission down here?
I think my mission is to find a wand.
With some...
Ad mana.
That is one of the biggies.
Or...
What was the other thing I really wanted?
Maybe some add damage.
That would be sick.
Whoops.
I'm so scared.
How are they not dead?
Wow.
Haha, what a shit show.
Should I be here?
Eh, let's go back.
Hello.
It shoots so fast.
Oh, I see!
The sniper killed his own.
Very cool.
This wand is violent.
Look at all that gold.
155 HP, not bad at all.
Holy shit.
You blow them up completely and they turn into mush.
Hello, sniper.
Wait, what the fuck was that spell just now?
Someone is throwing spells.
Makes me uneasy.
Oh no, it's a missile.
Wait, is it from there?
Ok, mana up, mana up.
Did he die?
Ok, nothing there.
I love exploring the Heezy base.
I think it's my favorite area.
It's so much fun.
Nice.
I love when that situation where you're just waiting for them to come out one by one and you just pick them off.
Feels incredible.
What's going on here?
Treasure chest!
Whoa!
Hello!
I almost missed that, that was so hard to spot, wow.
Did I miss all that gold?
Dammit.
How do I only have 400?
I feel like I've killed a bunch of enemies.
Come on.
Nice.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, baby.
Oh no!
Oh wait, I'm immune!
But I'm not immune to the freezing.
That's the only thing.
Look at this thing.
It's wild.
It's gonna explode.
Fucking propane tanks, man.
Pain of my existence.
Get out of here, propane tank.
Nobody likes you.
I can get in there though.
They have it hard in there!
I have a plan, I have a plan.
Let me first get rid of these things.
You're there.
Hands up.
Whoa!
Shit!
I just took a lot of damage there.
How do I best deal with that?
Oh shit.
Get rid of the freezing vapor.
I'm gonna invade these guys from the side here.
And kill them with the thing, look.
It's actually so good.
Oh!
I almost killed myself!
Shit!
Let's be really careful, huh?
God damn.
Damn.
There's still a guy down there.
I feel like I should not use my laser cutter anymore.
In this level.
Sweet.
No more laser cutting.
We're done with that right now.
Until things have settled.
Unless I really need to use it.
And I of course will use it.
Oh!
If I hadn't jumped, I think I would have died.
The electricity spread all across here along the steel beam.
And I was standing on it.
God damn.
Is there anything in there for me?
What's going on over there?
A sniper?
He's dead.
What do we got up here?
Okay.
Play real slow now.
Find some wants.
Come here.
Bro, the speed up on this is changing.
It's making it so much better.
This wouldn't be the same at all without that.
Okay.
I think I want at least a thousand before I move on, though.
And I gotta explore this base completely before I leave.
I mean, come on.
It's the easy base.
The easy base.
Perkele.
How do I...
I have to use my thing.
That's okay.
Just be really safe with it.
Stand here.
Aim it away from yourself.
Do not walk.
Be very smooth in your operation.
Very good.
And that's how we do it.
Now we wait for that guy to come over here.
I'm gonna teach him a lesson.
That guy's gonna turn around when he sees me.
No, unless...
No, no, I'm gonna...
Oh wait, this guy's gonna come up first?
Okay.
Good.
Ah, shit, he turned.
The water blocked that.
Haha.
Okay.
It's going well.
What else do I have here?
I have concentrated mana.
I actually have berserkium.
I should try and use that some more.
Do I want to go down there?
Does blood make me resistant to fire?
It does, it does.
Good.
Where did all this fire come from?
Ah, here we go.
It's one time, baby.
Let's see what we got.
Oh, we've got enemies.
Let's clear out that first.
What else do we see?
Flamethrower.
Water to poison and quadruple.
I don't like any of that.
Unfortunately.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Like, maybe there's stuff inside of these little areas there.
There could be a chest or something.
Oh, there's a turret.
Yeah, this water is moving around.
I don't like that.
I mean, the flame is moving around in the blood.
That's how we do it.
Looks like blood is very flammable.
Unless that's mixed with oil.
It is, okay.
We've got a turret in there.
Which way is it facing?
I can't tell.
Shit.
It's facing that way, I think.
I'm so scared of this laser.
Come on.
Through the choke hold.
I mean, choke point.
Let's go.
Form an orderly line.
Looks like they can't hurt each other with that beam, huh?
I want to kill that guy.
Oh, lots of fire.
I see electricity.
Oh, shit.
I had no more levitation.
Come on.
There we are.
Ooh, 54 HP.
Every single life point counts.
What's that?
The hell is that?
It's growing.
It's wobbling.
There's jiggle physics on it.
Oh, shit.
Wait, block?
I guess there must be an explosive effect on those shells he's shooting.
Fireworks.
This is a mess.
I'm tempted to go through.
I think I should.
43.
Yeah.
Do it.
Our weaponry is decent.
Okay, let's see what we got.
Give me something incredible, please.
I do like the electric thing.
Now that we are explosion immune.
Another speed up.
Okay.
I'm not sure I like any of that.
Projectile eater.
Projectiles that fly into a small sector behind a view disappear.
What?
Okay.
Never skip leg day.
Oh, no.
I'm not sure I like any of these, man.
Hmm.
I'm tempted to get this just because of the electric thingy.
But I just don't have the want to sustain it.
And I'm doing decent damage right now anyway.
It's not the best, but I think I'm going to re-roll here.
Let's see.
Levitation trail.
Wait, what's happening?
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
That guy is...
I'm on fire suddenly.
That guy is very resistant.
I'm going to have trouble down there for sure.
I can't even kill that guy reliably.
Oh, no.
What's this?
Spontaneous generation.
Bomb it near you?
No.
Hmm.
Worms find you attractive.
I don't like this.
I don't like any of this.
I feel like I'm coming back later.
I got to come back later.
Five hundred monies.
The only one I can buy is this.
And that doesn't look good either.
Welp.
That kind of sucks.
What else can I do?
Nah.
I'm moving on.
Coming back here to grab another re-roll.
And I am so slow from this slime.
Let's go.
Underground jungle.
That was the name.
You know what?
Let me change that.
Underground jungle.
There's no adepts.
I just want to call this the right thing, you know?
I remember there was something in front.
Whoops.
Under...
...ground...
...jungle.
Just gonna...
...like that, make it a little bit bigger.
There we go.
The underground jungle.
Nice.
Okay.
Let's keep moving.
Let's get rid of this.
Ee!
I don't like fire.
I still have black holes.
I have to remember that.
What's up, dudes?
Yeah, see, these guys take a lot of shots.
It's annoying.
And I'm gonna be on fire in just a second here.
Look how much HP this guy, dude, has.
Ugh.
I believe, though.
I believe we can find something down here.
Something that will aid us in our journey.
That's a spider.
Uh...
Let's stay on the top floor first.
Okay, that's where I entered.
In fact, let me get through here.
Jesus.
Did...
Whoa!
Man, this one is digging hardcore in this place.
Because it's all vegetation.
Oh, what the hell?
Oh, no.
Oh, I'm gonna fucking die here.
There's no way.
How am I not...
How am I gonna survive this place?
There's no way.
I gotta play this so safe.
Recharge mana?
Hahaha, the mind hit him, I think.
He hit himself.
No, wait, he's still alive.
Unless that's a friend.
Will you please die already?
Jesus.
I won!
What do we got?
Nothing we got.
It's terrible.
There's a flower over there.
That...
Oh, it's a frog.
Oh, there's mushrooms.
We could get high.
Should we try?
I'm gonna try and get high.
I just need to clear this area first.
You gotta...
You gotta be in a safe area when you go tripping, you know?
Oh my god.
How is that guy not dead yet?
I hit him one million times.
He's still alive.
And I'm on fire.
He finally died.
What is that?
Concentrate mana.
Sweet.
Test.
If I stand in it.
Yo!
Infinite shooting from here.
Oh no.
We've got a Loki!
Finish word for spider.
I'm just utterly destroying this place.
And you know what?
It makes me happy.
Let's eat the mushrooms.
Let's see what happens now.
Tripping.
Oh, look at the screen.
Oh, we're getting high, bitches.
Eat it all!
Listen, let me pay attention to the text now.
And...
Do I need to eat more?
Whoa.
You sense the reality has shifted.
You hear the word lava.
Something.
Fuck!
Why is it so quick?
I can't read it, man!
Oh wait, wait, wait, wait.
F11.
Oh, it doesn't show the text.
Never mind.
Whoa, the sounds!
Whoa.
I have been tripping.
We just went on a crazy trip.
And something about lava.
It wasn't copper this time.
So it's different every time.
Oh shit, wait, wait.
Crap, that.
I really should be remembering that I have stainless armor.
So...
I just don't know of a good way to get rid of stains quick.
Other than just moving.
Like I normally do all the time anyway.
Come on, explode that mind, please.
Make the jungle safe again.
Oh!
Oh my god.
Stop hitting me with that.
Please.
Oh, it's a dude with a...
growth on his head.
That makes me unhappy.
Look at all that gold.
Okay, I'm gonna go to a trip again.
If I find more mushrooms here.
Whoa!
I'm losing way too much HP.
Okay, I see a bunch here.
Oh yeah.
I'm in the jungle.
I'm on fire.
I have no more water.
I'm out of water.
Get in the mana.
Get me the mana.
Mana?
Water?
Where's water?
I'm on fire.
God damn it!
This is a problem.
This ain't good.
Where do we have water?
Oh, I'm tripping hard.
Oh shit.
I couldn't find more mushrooms sometime.
I love the muffled sound effects here.
They please me greatly.
I'm on fire again and I don't have any water, so...
Shit.
This is the problem with this weapon.
It produces fire everywhere in this place because it's all vegetation.
Show me the mushrooms.
I'm not done.
So violent.
What's this?
Eldritch portal?
Energy orb?
Plasma beam?
Like hole?
Nah.
I mean, the wand itself is actually sick.
That is a great wand right there.
Hello?
792.61?
That is...
That's sick.
I think I'm just gonna throw away those...
Oh, wait a minute.
Hold on, hold on.
Hold that thought, hold that thought.
Let's deal with these fuckers first.
Okay, so we have a nice wand.
We just need good spells.
Oh, that was an explosion.
Oof.
There's enemies everywhere.
Get away from me.
Get away from me!
Get in the blood, get in the blood.
Oh, my god.
I am fighting for my life here.
Shit ain't easy.
Let me tell you.
What's burning?
Oh, shit.
All the sand.
Whatever that is.
Not you, not you.
I know I should be picking up blood.
Just anything.
Anything I can douse myself with.
What the hell?
What are you shooting there?
Confusion?
No, wait, it's the poison!
Oh, no!
Oh, I'm fucking dead.
I'm actually dead.
What do I do?
I can't get rid of it.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
The plan...
is to get out of here.
And I mean, out of here, immediately.
We gotta get to a portal right now, otherwise this run is over.
Go through the part we've already been through.
Oh, shit, there's more enemies.
If I'm on fire, I'm fucked.
I need that blood, right now.
Grab it.
Pick it up, pick it up.
Good, good, good, good, good.
And that.
This has become survival.
This is no longer exploration.
We are out of here.
Just go down, I guess.
We gotta get to the portal.
That will explode, right?
Oh, shit.
Where'd that guy even come from?
Portal, please.
Oh, it's too quiet, it's way too quiet.
Hemis.
A single Hemis.
What is that down there?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Destroy it.
I see you there.
Porta.
Oh.
Oh, no.
I see the portal, though.
Did he die?
Okay, the guy's there.
No, I'm gonna jump into the portal.
Fuck everything else.
Here we go.
Oh.
Get the health, quick.
Whoo!
Man, oh, man.
Oh, nice.
We got healing, boys.
Aiming arc?
All seeing eye could be nice.
What's this?
Just water.
It's just water.
Nice.
Let's see the perks.
Permanent shield.
Oh, fuck.
I forgot to go back and reroll the other perks, didn't I?
God.
Wait, what's this?
The reality has shifted.
You sense things are no longer what they used to be.
Okay, so it was something about lava, right?
Something about lava.
Permanent shield.
That's good!
Dude, perm- Yes!
I love the permanent shield.
I'm definitely buying this.
Holy shit, I'm buying that.
That's incredible.
Uh, I don't want this.
Throw that crap away.
Get it out of my sight.
The Eldritch Portal, get it out of my sight!
Well, maybe it's good, but...
I tried it once and I thought I could go through it and go somewhere else.
It turned out someone else came through and fucked me up.
So, yeah, that was fun.
Plasma beam.
I'm not sure about that.
I think I tried it once.
I wasn't impressed.
My coal is good to have, I guess.
I mean, whatever.
What is this?
Giant Spitterbolt?
I don't think I've ever seen that.
Oh, I don't have enough money anyway.
Alright, we can't buy anything else.
It is what it is.
Uh...
This wand, though.
This wand slaps.
261 mana charge, compared to this- Oh my god, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, this is gonna be so much better.
We can almost spam that shit.
Actually, we can spam that shit.
So that means we can maybe go nuts here.
Add more damage.
Okay, that drain's quick.
That still drains so quick, wow.
Not worth it.
No, that's way too slow.
This is still the best, I think.
Yeah, it's still the best.
And the good part is, it's no longer gonna explode and make fire everywhere.
Fuck yeah.
You know what?
How- Someone did- What?
Uh...
Someone did something somewhere.
And I don't understand it.
But sure.
This right here.
Yeah!
Oh, but the issue is, we're gonna be stained all the time.
And that's bad with our stainless armor.
Maybe I'll put this on...
What about this?
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Let me see how this does.
No.
I do like the idea of having water immediately, because that will take out fire on me, right?
Maybe just have it like that and then put- This is my- Oh shit, I'm on fire button now.
Oh wait, that explodes.
Yikes.
That's an explodey wand.
Iceball!
Aiming.
What is happening?
What's happening?
Why are the gods suddenly so angry?
Or not angry, they- Yeah, I guess they are angry, but they look the other way, right?
Maybe they didn't like that I put water in here?
No.
I don't know what I should take.
Maybe this?
Let me try this.
Nah.
Not really that cool.
Unless it would be better with something else.
Bro, is water just absorbing all of this?
That's really bad.
In fact, you know what?
Let me drain this.
I need to get out of here anyway.
Yeah, now they are angry.
They don't like that I destroy their property.
The holy mountain.
Mountain.
Let me go to the other statue.
This looked like a new spell for a second.
Like a plasma with a thing in between.
That just confused me.
Okay.
No, that sucks.
What about- What about this one, actually?
No.
Bad.
Is this going to change anything if I- Wow, the bandy, the accelerated homing is absolute trash.
But I guess it could be cool if I had a rock and I had infinite spells.
That is the only thing.
Okay.
These go up here.
And in this one, I'm going to- I'm just going to- Ah, the healing, of course.
Healing on that one.
There we go.
Oh, but wait, that's going to explode every time?
I don't like that.
I don't like that at all.
I don't have another wand, though.
Wait, is that going to explode on me, then?
Oh, but wait, I'm immune to explosion.
It's fine.
Well, this is going to put me on fire.
But I could always do it in water, then.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Everything's fine.
Also, I'm still carrying this around for some reason.
If all the mountains were of silver and gold, what would they profit?
A man who lives in constant fear of death.
Hence, there cannot be in the whole world anything better than our medicine, which has power to heal all the diseases of the flesh.
Can I have access to that medicine?
Because...
I feel like I need it.
The vault.
That's right.
That was the name.
Hold on.
The vault.
Let's write that.
This is...
the vault.
I don't know if these sizes are accurate, but I feel like they are sort of...
representative here.
You know?
So, hold on a second.
Snowy depths...
actually connects, right?
To this.
Fire up there, or the lava.
So, really...
it's something like...
let me erase here.
Let me do, I guess, this part here.
Take that away.
Somewhere there.
It sort of does one of these, right?
It goes...
like this.
I'm making it a rocket, because it's like, rock terrain down there.
Maybe to...
like, here.
Because up here...
we have a bridge.
Right?
It goes across like that.
Let me zoom in on that a little bit, so I can draw this better.
Something like that.
I'm just gonna draw a nice bridge there.
And then there's a huge chasm underneath that, right?
With the wall going like this.
And then at some point...
there is actually a...
little room.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I remember now, I remember now.
I remember now.
Hold on.
This is wrong.
Whoops.
Not that one.
Give me the red one.
And then we have to adjust this.
This is actually a much bigger basin.
Because this connects all the way to that little room.
Yeah, I'm slowly filling this out, dude.
Let's see here.
I think it's more like...
It goes down like that.
And then at some point, it's sort of...
I guess it makes one of these?
Because...
there's a cave?
Right?
Hold on.
Let me just go up a bit more.
There's a cave where...
How do I draw this better?
Hmm, wait a minute.
I guess I could always draw this when I get...
You know what?
I'm gonna draw this when I get there.
Just so I can make it precise.
But there's a little place where I found...
And there's a little place with lava there, where it sort of...
goes in.
Yeah.
We're gonna do that later when I get up there.
Because I'm gonna get back up there.
For sure.
Now that the gods can look the other way...
I think we're good.
But the only problem we have in this run...
is that we don't really do a lot of damage.
And our wands kind of suck.
Everything else is aligned.
Everything else is great.
It's just that one little detail, you know, of having shitty wands.
Oh my god, oh my god!
What the hell?
Okay, I feel like I'm doing way less damage now that the explosive effect is gone.
Am I crazy?
Oh, that guy is...
Oh, this is bad.
A wand suck!
At least I got that guy.
Good news is there's no more recoil.
Look how much HP he has.
I can't kill him.
This is gonna be an uphill battle.
Come on, there's gotta be a better way.
There's gotta be a better wand I can make out of this stuff.
I have so much crab up here.
It's gotta be possible...
to make something...
with a kick to it.
Right?
I don't... I don't... Honestly, I don't see anything.
We have to find a wand.
We have to find better spells.
So, plate safe, plate slow.
And we have healing.
Don't forget, we have healing.
Blood is fine.
We can have blood on us.
Okay, so let's see.
Maybe it's better if I use my plasma thing on it.
Jesus!
It's gonna take a while.
At least that guy dies quick.
And that is a shit... Oh no, I don't have water, so...
I guess there was a bit of water in there.
HP!
It's been a fucking minute.
Nice!
Haven't seen one of those in ages.
But I guess I did make my way through the areas quick.
Because I almost died immediately, every time.
This wand is complete and utter trash.
I need something else.
I need something else, real bad.
Fuck!
That will do the trick.
Better than nothing.
Uh oh.
Oh, he's blocking attacks with those hands.
I kick it up!
Sir?
Where's the handman?
Handman?
I think he's over here somewhere.
There's a lot of knockback on this weapon.
But I do no damage.
I wonder if the knockback is because of the speed up I have.
Oh no!
It's electrified!
That's a death trap!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We can't, we can't, we can't dead.
No, no, no.
We gotta, we gotta fix that.
How do I fix that?
Oh, I'm slippery.
God.
Oh no!
My worst nightmare.
Has arrived.
Thank God they die quick.
Okay.
Yikes.
What the hell is that?
I, I can't kill anything.
What do I do?
What do I do, man?
Maybe I go another way.
Let's see over here if there's a wand.
That guy's never gonna die.
Oh wait.
Oh!
He dispatches his head!
That's how that works.
That's funny.
His head comes off.
His head disappeared.
And reappeared.
I gotta heal.
I think I should heal now.
Thankfully the explosive effect didn't do anything.
Nevermind.
It did.
But I'm immune, so.
We are Gucci.
Oh!
Oh no.
He's gonna hit me with that bullshit.
I don't like that at all.
Hello?
Nice.
I'm focusing so much.
You have no idea.
I am in gamer mode right now.
Money!
Also, we still have a perk somewhere, right?
That we never re-rolled?
I never went back, right?
Because I didn't have the money?
Oh, dude.
I'm tempted to go back.
We can dig, right?
Technically we have the plasma.
We could go back.
Watch this.
Let's see what we got.
Disc projectile.
Large magic missile.
Let's see the wand itself.
The wand itself is not bad.
But I don't think I...
These are not the things that will do a big thing for me here, you know?
What is this blue stuff?
Oh shit!
Teleportitis.
I thought it was mana.
God damn it.
Okay, it's gone.
That could have been bad.
Oh!
The worm!
Oh my god, the spiders!
That's why the gods were so angry.
It's not just if I break the stuff here, it's if anyone breaks it.
That's perfect, though.
I wanted to be here again because...
Man, will you die?
What the hell?
What are you even?
Have I ever seen you?
Nice, gotcha.
Alright, I'm going back up.
This is a much safer area, actually, compared to the other one.
Oh!
Sick!
Hello!
There it is.
Look at that.
Reroll that crap.
What do we got?
What's this?
High mana, low capacity.
You're currently held one, loses half...
Holy fuck!
Are you kidding me?
This one was definitely more effective with the explosive modifier on it.
Ugh.
What if I eat this?
Food poisoning.
Then we have boomerang spells.
Your spells...
Man.
Wait.
High mana, low capacity.
You're currently held one, loses half its capacity, but gains more mana.
No.
That's a new one.
I haven't seen that before, but no.
Your spells arcs towards you, but gain extra speed and deal extra damage.
Nah.
Hungry ghost?
Someone's a happy minion who eats enemy protectile every now and then.
I don't like any of these, man.
Fuck!
I could come back later and re-roll it.
But, you know what?
I should try new things.
I'm gonna try this, because if it eats projectiles, that could protect me.
And in combination with my current shield, maybe it's insane.
Who knows?
Um...
So here's the plan.
I will actually go back up one level and explore that fully.
So I can find more wands.
Now that I have healing and all that, and I have refreshers...
Oh my god, I have a bunch of healing then.
Hell yeah!
I'm gonna do that.
Let me just see if there's a worm who did some stuff over here, because maybe that will help me.
Can I please get rid of this slime, dammit?
There it is, look.
Someone's a happy minion who'll eat enemy protectile every now and then.
Only every now and then.
I regret taking this now.
Oh my god.
Get this slime.
Oh, I can just go underwater, of course.
There we go.
I will dig from... let's say here.
Gonna take a while.
Let's not damage ourselves.
I figured out a nice technique with this though.
Yeah, the gods are angry.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, they are so mad.
Uh, stand here.
Just for safety.
By the way, I think I realize why I take damage sometimes when I use this to dig down.
The reason is I destroy the ground below me and I fall down into the beam.
So I am hyper aware of that now.
Yeah, made it.
I'm back.
And now my spells are not useless anymore.
Well, I guess they're a little less useful because...
I had the explosive effects last time here.
Let me just...
Whoa, okay.
Why did that die so quick?
That was weird.
Whoa!
What the fuck is that?
I've never seen that.
It's a plasma beam green turret thingy.
Wow.
Oh, you're gonna burn?
It does know how to shoot up, it seems.
Uh, hungry ghost, will you please absorb the fucking projectiles like you said you would?
This is a betrayal.
No, I'm not gonna get that money.
Play it safe.
What's up, my dude?
Uh, give me that blood.
I collect the blood of my enemies.
Oh, here we go.
The gang is there.
Timmy, Tommy, Robbie and Jimmy.
What the hell?
He had a wand.
And he had a good wand, I think.
Excuse me, guys.
This is insanity.
Holy fucking shit.
Look at all this blood!
Wow, what a slaughter!
Thunder charge!
A hundred and twenty mana drain, though.
That could be nice.
Maybe I take that?
Oh, but I need to get rid of a wand, then.
Let's try and remember where this is, approximately.
Let's retrace our steps when we walk from here.
In fact, let's make it back to the holy mountain up here.
Although, do we want to play with electricity?
That's scary.
That really is scary.
So far, so good.
I have faith...
that this will turn out to be great.
Those things will fucking electrify things.
If you're not careful.
Oh, here comes the gang.
This hungry ghost, I haven't seen it do anything.
But maybe I'm wrong.
There's a bunch of shit happening on the screen, right?
It's hard to tell.
Maybe it's been saving my life this entire time, and I wouldn't even know.
I can get in here.
I have spells up there.
What's up, guys?
How is it hanging?
Choke point.
Actually, really effective strategy.
That should do it.
That guy just clipped into the wall.
Good thing we can do that, too.
Like shooting fish in a barrel.
That's the perfect description of this.
Whoa.
Why is there so much blood, man?
This seems like verta, verta, verta.
And I don't have that.
I guess I'd just be killing like that.
I do be killing like that.
Let me go down.
Just be careful now when we stand up here.
That's why I do it at an angle like this.
Who else wants some?
You, sir.
How about a shave?
Cool.
Notice how much more safe I am this time around in Heezy Base.
Because I don't have the explosive modifier.
And I don't set fire to everything.
They're going to die in the freezing vapor, too.
Idiots.
Uh-huh.
I see something up there.
Oh, hello there.
There were a bunch of people.
I'm going to kill that.
Oh, wait.
This thing reflects, right?
Oh, no.
You can actually destroy it.
Oh, wow.
I guess you remove the shield first and then the next projectile hits it.
Get out of here.
Oh, wait.
This is the end anyway.
I see dense rock.
That's a bomb.
I want?
Huh.
Uh, no.
Not a mana, though, but very shitty recharge.
Oh, that's toxic sludge.
I feel like such an excavator when I use my plasma cutter, it feels...
Whoa, what the hell?
Yo!
A store!
Yo, what the hell's that?
Plasma beam enhancer!
Whoa!
Short-range homing?
Dude.
Does that work on plasma cutter, too?
Makes plasma beams spell...
It better work.
Let's get rid of...
um, that one.
I kind of want to buy...
this one.
To have.
That one could be nice.
Maybe I'll buy that, too.
Yeah, why not?
Let's get rid of something else, like heavy spread.
There we go.
Also, is there anything else?
Let me take a look around.
What is that sound I'm hearing?
You hear that sound?
There it was again.
Weird.
It's just me.
I'm making the droplet sound with my mouth.
People don't believe me when I say that.
It's true.
Who else wants them?
I don't know.
Habra, habra, habra, habra.
Oh my god.
Propite tank is very wild.
Look at that beauty.
It sucks.
Whoa!
Jump up!
Goddamn!
That was a disaster.
That thing's gonna... get it out of here.
Explode, please.
There we go.
It is now gone.
Whoa.
There we go.
Taking care of.
Swimming in blood.
Why is there so much blood?
I feel like I've picked up a verta, verta, verta somehow.
I see electricity.
And it scares me quite a lot.
Should I?
Yeah.
Oh!
Wow, we didn't die from that.
Oh my god, stop!
Okay, I think I'm gonna heal when I'm at 30%.
Damn.
Somehow that guy died quicker than normal.
That's a bomb.
There's another bomb.
Whoa!
Oh, maybe I just crit him.
That's probably what happened.
Uh...
So many explosives.
All things considered, this is a decent one for this area.
I can... I can fuck with it.
Okay.
Wait, there's a dark area here.
Oh!
Hello.
Wait a minute.
What's happening here?
What's with all the snow?
Oh!
Treasure chest!
Why is there so much blood?
A wand!
Pollen.
There's a lot of mana though, on that wand.
It's not the worst.
Definitely not the best either.
Uh-oh.
Fire spreading!
Ah, shit.
I gotta take the other path.
I don't want to swim in that.
Okay.
What's happening here?
I absolutely love exploring.
Such a rewarding feeling.
Just cleanse these areas.
I would love to find more HP.
And then down the road, find one of those that increases your current HP by 50%.
Now that's the way.
Bunch of blood here too.
Oh, wait a minute.
See, this looks suspicious down here, doesn't it?
In fact, am I seeing something?
Hold on.
What?
I didn't even see that!
God damn!
There's a propane tank?
I'm blind, I guess.
There's something in there.
You know what, I bet there's something in that snow.
Watch this.
Something's hiding in that snow.
Maybe.
I guess we release the blood.
And that will feel good.
Yeah, sure.
Let me quickly go up where I came from here.
Look at the scorch marks here.
Let's see what I have going here.
I don't think there was anything crazy here that I really would like.
Maybe the...
Maybe I'll take that.
Oh, let's try this!
Plasma beam enhancer.
Nah, it only works with a plasma beam, I guess.
It makes sense, I guess.
This is a plasma cutter, it's not a plasma beam.
Damn it.
I'm gonna heal.
And then I'm gonna grab this.
Nice.
Those refreshers are gonna be so valuable.
Uh, you know what?
Let me just go straight up again.
Same place.
I think we're sort of powerful enough to explore.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we're going.
Dude, we're going.
Oh, I know you're angry, I know you're angry.
Too fucking bad.
Oh.
Let me go a little further down.
I'm just a tad too scared here.
I feel like I should make this a little more easy to traverse in case I need to go back down.
No, wait a minute, I can always use the portal.
Yeah, fuck that.
Am I crazy or is this plasma cutter worse than before?
I feel like it cuts way worse.
This area I didn't get to explore very much.
Because I was very underpowered at this point and I was low HP and it was catastrophic all around.
But now, I'm back.
And I'm gonna fuck shit up.
That guy still has a lot of HP.
Oh my god.
Will you not?
I need to use my teleport offensively in combat.
It's really good for that.
Especially those turrets to get on the other side so they have to slowly rotate their turret.
Very cool.
That guy is frozen?
Is it the ghost making that sound?
Like a rear, rear...
Sup fool?
Heh heh.
What's that?
Polymorphine?
That's right, I don't like that.
We do not like that.
Ah!
Something up there.
Drain it.
Huh.
Something exploded.
If I'm lucky, I find a wand with add mana, that would be...
Or honestly, even better, the damage modifier.
That would slap with the wand I have right now.
Imagine that.
So now I'm in the snowy depths.
Now we can map out this area precisely.
Look at this.
It goes up like that.
And this is now the place.
Oh, so it's like at the top.
Okay, so actually, good thing I came back here and checked.
So it goes all the way over here.
And does sort of that thing.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's go map this out, huh?
So the roof is here.
And then it goes...
From the roof.
It does that.
Okay.
Hold on.
Let's make that drawing now.
Yeah, so I was wrong about this.
See, this is why you don't do it from memory.
Memory is bad.
Delete that.
Okay.
So it basically goes like this.
Hold on.
Remove this part.
So this is the roof of snowy depths, right?
It kind of goes like that.
Then over here it goes up like this.
And joins with that.
Right?
Yes.
Now we have the bridge up there.
And then down here.
It actually...
It kind of looks like it sort of does this.
And then it does that.
You know, then it joins over here.
I'm making it like rocky on the bottom there.
I'm not drawing a straight line on purpose.
Just to make it look nice, I guess.
And then it... Okay, to that point.
Gotcha.
We got to remove a little bit.
I don't even know if you can see that.
There we go.
Like there.
One more.
There we go.
Now we draw up.
Whoops.
Approximately this way.
Cool.
Look at how well this all fits.
Coal pits.
So does that?
Hmm.
Yes.
And now we're going to find this room.
And then we can fill up the rest.
Yep.
That's the plan.
So we go up until we can hear.
Wait, why is this all...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
What's this?
Why does that look like that?
Oh, wait a minute.
Huh?
Uh...
What the fuck is this?
This is new.
What the hell is this?
What is that?
Wait, what, what is it?
Can I kick you?
The hell?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What is that?
It's some kind of puzzle.
No, wait, wait, what?
Oh!
Wait, what?
It's rotating with my cursor.
Oh, wait, what?
It's like a little... racetrack.
Oh my god, this is so weird.
Hold on.
Huh?
I think I'm stuck.
Why is it going that way?
Huh?
I'm so confused.
Well...
I feel like this is some sort of easter egg.
Oh wait, here we go, here we go.
Wait a minute.
If I do a lap...
Am I gonna get something?
This is really difficult.
Oh my god.
This is very hard to control.
Sometimes the mouse is like...
Okay, this is weird.
I don't understand what's happening.
I'm gonna leave.
Alright, man.
It's actually still...
Wait, it's still with me.
What if I...
Ah!
Hello!
What is this, man?
Okay, but...
Let's log that!
Let's log that shit!
That's awesome!
And that's further down.
Now we can hear the thing I was actually looking for.
Okay, so it's sort of...
Hold on.
It's like a little...
I guess...
Path in here.
And then it's...
It's like a little...
In fact, this is like...
Kinda hidden, isn't it?
There's this sort of thing in front you have to destroy.
I'm gonna do that.
And there's this weird...
Place in here.
And then in the center...
It's like a little room.
There we go!
I'm gonna call it...
Racetrack!
Amazing!
And then further up...
In fact, let me put that below.
So we have some room here.
This must be really close, then.
How much shit is hidden in this game?
Now I wonder, you know?
Like...
I just randomly found that stuff.
This is it.
That could be stuff everywhere in any place.
Like, this was inside some dense rock.
Wait, where is it?
Below,
or...?
There's the racetrack.
I think it's above.
It's above.
Oh yeah, it's getting louder.
There it is!
Familiar orb of true knowledge.
What?!
Hello!
Wait a minute!
I understand!
The reality has shifted.
Lava is now poison?
Everywhere?
That's fucking crazy!
Dude...
We need to be tripping some more.
That is awesome!
What if that turned into water?
I guess it's randomized.
Last time?
Okay, so the first time I did that...
It said copper.
So I guess copper must have turned into something else.
Or shifted into something else.
Reality has shifted.
Dude...
That is awesome!
But...
Hold on.
Now we gotta fill this out.
Let's see...
It's probably like here.
Let me see...
There's my pen.
Actually, I kinda forgot what it looked like already.
It was like...
Okay, so sort of...
That's...
Gotcha.
So it goes down like this, right?
And then here...
It sort of does that.
But no, it actually...
Yeah, that's actually fine.
It doesn't go all the way there, it goes to here.
And then...
It sort of does something like that.
No.
Something like...
Nah...
Like that, maybe?
It's the only way that makes sense.
So if you make...
I'm just gonna put lava here, of course.
Even though it's not lava now, but it usually is.
So it goes like here.
You know?
Look at that.
That is the layout.
Boys and girls.
And then this one is actually closed off like that.
Hidden in there.
And then...
We can also write...
Yellow.
Whoops.
Didn't mean to fill that out.
Plus HP and...
A green tablet.
There it is.
Cool!
And this one is...
Honestly, the racetrack is...
question marked for me, like what the hell is going on there?
That is some weird stuff.
Alright!
Poison, huh?
What if I put blood in there?
Hmm.
What if I put concentrated mana in there?
Wait!
Yo, it's changing!
Blood did something!
Hello!
Hey!
No way!
Did I just discover something?
Come on!
How was it this one?
Wait, how did I do that?
What did I...
How did I just make this disappear?
Huh?
Wait a minute.
I have no idea how I just did that.
I guess I can...
get rid of it like this.
I'm removing all the poison.
Oh shit, oh shit, oh shit.
Yeah, that's scary.
Uh, if I had a bomb, I would love to try a bomb here.
I don't know what I...
The blood must have done something.
I think it's still sort of evaporating here.
Look, it's turning into gas.
Slowly but surely, this thing is being emptied, I think.
Goddamn.
Okay.
I'm just gonna keep going.
Let me see what's on this again.
Heat my warning or death and decay will follow.
I feel like I should put this in the right order at some point.
So we have volume one, two, three and all that.
So this is emerald tablet.
Heat my warning.
Who are you to write that thing?
Huh?
Who are you, buddy?
Tell me your name.
I wish to know everything.
I wish to know about your dad.
Think about your dad.
What's your dad like?
Come here, little buddy.
We're going on an adventure.
I kind of want to fly this thing into an enemy.
Oh, look, yeah, I'm right.
It's all going away.
Motherfucker.
Holy shit.
This is nuts.
Look.
Yep.
It's all gone, baby.
Kind of want to use this opportunity to explore as much as I can.
Let's try and listen.
Let's try and pay attention to any and all hints here.
I don't immediately... Okay, so here's the thing.
The health that I just found inside the little area.
You could find that by listening.
That was a distinct sound, right?
The racetrack I found because everything looked a little half destroyed already in the rock.
So there are like indicators that you should be digging.
But I don't see any of those here.
Hmm.
Where's my little buddy?
He must have gone up somewhere.
I imagine.
Ah, there he is.
You want to come with me?
This way?
There's no way.
I'm trying to guide him right now.
Imagine where he is.
Ah, fuck it.
I'm moving along.
So now I want to try something crazy.
Now I'm finally back up here, right?
What I want to try is...
I'm going to bring a tablet to the ocean hut.
That's the ancient laboratory.
I want to do that.
The demon eye platforms.
Dark area.
We could do that.
Because I have a light and I have access to a holy mountain.
Eat more shrooms.
That one is done, baby.
Oh.
There we go.
Okay.
Let's go to the...
Go to the ocean hut.
I actually have one with me already.
Tabula smaractina.
Oh, I kind of want to bring both just in case.
Hold on, I found another one down here.
Here.
Let's get rid of berserkium.
Now I have both of these.
Tabula smaractina and the emerald tablet.
Man, teleport wand is incredible.
And we're back!
You know what?
I'm going to finally fuck this guy up now.
Yeah, you like that?
Bastard.
It's haunting me this entire time.
Finally, I got him.
I'm going to get that water.
Fill me up before I go-go.
Actually, hold on.
Isn't blood always better?
Blood takes out fire, but also gives me crit chance.
It's actually always better, no?
So, why did I just do that?
Oh man, is it bright?
We have emerged from the depths.
Hell yeah.
What the hell are you doing here?
Like, what?
Oh, what the- Say, what?
Whoa!
Huh?
Wait a minute, there's water here?
Hold on a second.
I don't have any memory of this.
Uh oh, tell me this air!
Oh god!
I can't remember if I found this.
Secretorum hermitis.
The sacrifice of oneself to the pursuit of knowledge is the highest tribute to the gods.
Okay.
So, in other words, go find more orbs.
Because you gained true knowledge.
Right?
So, if I sacrifice myself, in the pursuit of knowledge, meaning go find the orbs, that is the highest tribute to the gods.
You know what?
I'm taking that too.
And I'm gonna mark this.
Uh, where is it?
Here.
Man, I got that completely wrong, huh?
Get rid of this part.
And then it's sort of- down, I guess.
Uh, wait.
Goes up.
Okay, whoops.
And it does a weird...
thing where it sort of goes down like that, up to a small chamber.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, how does this make sense?
Wait a minute.
Right.
Okay.
So, it goes...
like that.
There.
And inside of here we have a little tablet.
Cool!
Cool burger.
Wait, what's that?
Oh, choose color?
No.
Uh, we are good.
Back to you.
Back to the desk.
I'm just gonna cut my way through here.
In fact, can't I just...
Ah, it's gonna take too long.
I'm so sorry, I'm just...
murdering this tree.
Yep, that thing is there.
In fact, since I'm here...
let me try all these.
Ah!
Oh, wait, they don't do anything.
Okay.
I had to try.
Let's put these eggs here, dude.
I mean, I guess if you just want a worm.
I should draw these pillars as well.
I can do that.
Oh, wait a minute.
Upside down triangle.
We saw that today.
That was the simp...
No, not quite the same symbol, I guess.
They didn't have the line through it.
But that symbol...
I think meant water in that case?
Because...
Whoa.
Where are you coming from?
What the hell?
Honestly, where the hell did you just come from?
All right.
Yeah, look at this.
I still haven't drawn that there's this in here.
I never did draw that in my map.
I'm going to do that later.
This is so mysterious, too.
I think it's like a little bit of an Easter egg.
You can...
play music, of course, with it.
But, yeah.
Okay.
I'm just going to leave that here for now.
I can always go grab it if I want it later.
I bet you...
I think I've said this before, but there's going to be a puzzle somewhere.
Where you have to play the right notes in the right order, and something will happen.
Okay.
Then we have...
Paasilme.
A demon eye or whatever.
On a...
Buried in the snow.
I will draw that.
In fact, I'm just going to draw it on top.
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
So there's sort of a...
pillar here.
Right?
There's sort of that.
That weird thing, and it loops like that.
And in here...
there's an eye.
Demon eye.
And it sits on top of some weird pillar buried in the snow.
I'm just going to write...
I don't know if this...
It probably doesn't mean demon eye, but that's what I call it.
Paasilme, I think.
Probably spelled that wrong.
Ah, I did.
I put the A in the wrong place.
Whatever!
But I know there's secrets with this one too, right?
This one produces platforms in the west.
Should I take it?
Maybe I should...
Ah, I don't have much space though.
I'll get rid of one of these tablets.
Maybe that one.
Please.
Just that way.
I'm taking it!
Let me try it here.
Okay.
I actually kind of forgot where it worked.
But on some platform somewhere, when I used it...
you could see these glowing platforms you could stand on.
And you could get all the way up.
But there were scary enemies there last time, so...
Wait, what's happening?
Did I just collapse all this with my one shot?
No way.
I keep thinking there's something below the snow because I can hear there's humming.
But it's the ghost following me.
The hungry ghost.
A happy minion.
It does kind of look happy, doesn't it?
Okay, so I definitely drew this landscape completely flat.
Even though it's hilly.
I think the hilliness is randomized, so I'm just going to keep it flat in my drawing.
That thing, though.
Essence eater.
I'm not entirely sure.
Oh wait, there's markings below it.
You see that?
Upside down triangles?
I wonder what that means.
Could the normal upside or the normal side triangle mean a mountain?
Oh man, it's getting all dark now.
Night is approaching.
I should call this ghost something.
What should your name be?
Maybe...
I like Sally.
You shall be known as Sally from now on.
Henceforth, that will be the indicator for you.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Huh.
I think I saw this last time.
And I don't understand it.
Why is it so dark?
Wait, where am I now?
Wait, what the?
Bridge?
Wait, I don't have any memory of this at all.
Wait a minute now.
What's happening here?
Hello?
I'll just have a quick peek.
Ah!
Also, I hear explosions.
We've got a wand.
Oh shit, oh shit, oh shit.
Frozen vault.
Holy... okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
I'm going to de-aggro these guys, if I can.
And then get back and steal that wand.
Frozen vault.
Yo, what?
Oh shit, oh shit.
How powerful are you?
Oh, you're very powerful.
Oh my God.
Jesus Christ!
Okay, those enemies don't fuck around.
Hot damn!
Yeah, we need more damage for sure.
This is some endgame shit right here.
My God.
Well, that works.
Slowly but surely.
I like that as soon as I popped in.
Oh no, one of them has the wand.
This guy has the wand.
Fuck!
He's probably super dangerous.
I think he just used the wand and there was some bullshit in that wand.
Are these guys friends to me?
I don't like that it's burning though.
Get away from me.
Shit.
Where's the wand?
Those guys are not too bad.
I can kill those, I think.
We should be okay on that front.
What's that?
Poison gas?
Okay.
Got a ghostbuster?
Oh, there he is, there he is.
Come on, minions.
I don't have no idea how these minions spawn, but...
I like that they're helping me.
Oh, nice, he died!
What do we got?
I figured.
Some kind of egg bullshit.
Okay, I don't care.
Get out!
All right, frozen vault, huh?
Good to know.
And what is down here?
Oh.
Is this the...
Wait.
Okay, they're not that bad.
They're not too bad.
I want...
Accelerating shot.
Random projector.
I don't like random.
I don't.
Random is bad, bro.
Is this still the frozen vault?
Oh, what is that?
It explodes.
Wait, what's going on?
Did that guy just shoot his friend?
Oh,
no.
Not those guys.
Sally!
Help me!
Eat some spells, dammit!
Eat them!
Oh, not the froggies.
Maybe I shouldn't be here.
Kind of want to go to the ocean hut.
It's working out decently.
Oh, God, they're still frogs.
They are everywhere.
Something is down there.
Man, I kind of want to explore this a little bit because...
it seems like there are some crazy wands here.
There's a good chance I might find something nice.
It's like high risk, high reward, you know?
What is that thing?
Oh, what the hell?
Is that a barrier like my barrier?
Oh, yeah, it is.
Similar to my barrier, he has three of them.
Is he shooting his friend?
You like that?
Okay, I hid myself with that.
Okay!
What?
How am I supposed to kill you?
Doesn't do much to me, though.
Got it!
Okay, that guy has some armor.
Jesus.
Hey, froggy!
Hey there.
That guy is blocking everything I do.
Oh, no, not on one of those guys.
Oh, he was a lot easier.
It bounced off my shield!
That is lovely.
Who is shooting that?
It's you!
There we go.
Dude,
this is fucking awesome.
I'm exploring a whole new place.
Get rid of all the explosives.
Damn, what an explosive that is.
I hate these things so much.
Get rid of that fire.
These enemies seem a lot tougher than they are.
Like, I'm constantly scared, but then they turn out to be...
Okay, that guy is still a bit of a problem.
Why are they blocking everything?
Sometimes he blocks, sometimes he doesn't.
It's weird.
Oh, shit.
This is a mess.
That guy is totally immune to my shit.
Get up!
I mean, he doesn't really damage me.
It's weird.
They are taking damage, but...
Not sure...
Wait,
is that guy giving him a shield?
I think his teammate there is actually giving him the shield.
Oh, God, we need mana.
He's taking damage.
He's not doing anything to me, though.
Like, he's just sitting there.
Weird.
He's definitely some kind of buff enemy.
He buffs his friends.
I want to shoot that thing so bad.
Come on.
Once.
Spells.
Give me something.
Whoa!
Oh, I hate these guys.
I hate these guys.
I hate these guys so much.
Where are you?
Those guys are not too bad.
It's soon time to heal, I think.
Where's the electricity, man?
I can't hit anything.
Wow.
Come here.
Come here, you little fucker.
That works.
This guy is shooting fire at me.
Whoa!
Get plasmid.
I think he died, because they bleed diamonds.
So much HP.
I kind of want to give up on killing him.
There we go.
He wasn't really posing a threat.
Where am I, man?
Is this also the frozen vault?
I guess it is.
But there was also an ancient laboratory somewhere.
Kill him.
Oh, there you are.
What's that?
Toxic ice, yikes.
Don't like that.
Get away from me.
Froggers.
Frogster.
I think I'm going to heal.
No, I'm going to wait a bit.
Maybe until we're at 20% or something.
Then we heal.
I see things in there.
I kind of want to go in there.
Ha!
It's a crab!
That's the new enemy.
Cool.
Seeking missiles.
Oh my god.
The HP on this guy...
is kind of nuts.
Then again, I'm just doing very shitty damage.
Wow!
Okay, you know what?
Nope, this ain't happening.
I definitely don't have the damage for this place.
I'm going to get out of here.
I'm going to go to the ocean hut and do what I came here for in the first place.
Probably nothing's going to happen anyway.
I guess I can exit here.
Hey, look!
Peace!
Okay, the journey continues.
See, this right here is another indicator, I think.
That something's going on down here.
Yeah, see, this is totally leading me.
Ah, but you know what?
Let's not get distracted.
I'm going to go to the ocean hut.
I also want to experiment with those portals over there more.
This is it!
Watch!
If I do this...
isn't that weird?
And then you can go up on these platforms, and there's enemies up there.
But I think those enemies are crazy.
Entered lake.
Lakehouse, I guess.
More accurate than...
Then we have this book.
I have locked my research so that only those with...
Okay, let me try this first.
Ah, I fucking knew it!
Where?
Oh!
Uh...
That was an enemy.
Oh shit.
Can I use the other one?
Let's go.
Get up!
Come on, Sally!
Okay, nice, we got him.
What the hell is all this?
I'm burning, I'm burning!
Oh no.
What the hell?
Yellow glimmer?
Wait a minute.
Oh, wait.
Uh...
Gives a projectile a red sparkly trail.
It reduces castelay.
Huh.
Wow.
Like little easter egg area, maybe?
Eh.
Rainbow glimmer.
Randomly colored sparkly trail.
I'll take that.
Wait, what's the white one?
What's that one?
Uh, let me get rid of this again.
Let me see this one.
Turns a projectile invisible.
Huh.
I don't know if that's good or bad.
Maybe I like the rainbow more.
Let's try that, I guess, at some point.
Oh, imagine.
If you could fucking edit here.
Wait a minute, where am I right?
Oh, what's this?
Experimental wand!
Giant spitter bolt.
Huh.
Wait.
Cool.
Is the wand any good, though?
I don't like these spells on it.
I don't think I like it.
Where's my...
No.
I like...
I mean, it is better.
It is a better wand.
No, it's actually not a better wand.
Maybe it is.
I like how it looks, though.
So, wait, we're actually in that box down below.
But, when I went down like this...
Oh, wait, now it's...
What about the other one, though?
Okay.
If we put a tablet here of a different color, that will take us to the next...
place down here.
To the other portal.
That's what I think.
But I manually went down there last time and I didn't find anything.
So, putting this here actually spawned...
the stuff that I just found.
Cool.
I'll take that with me.
Kind of want to try going west.
Hold on, what else do I have on my list?
Mmm...
Demon Eye...
This one, done.
Can't believe that actually worked.
Explore Ancient Laboratory?
I can't remember where I found that.
I just remember the text popping up.
I'm pretty sure it was in that place I was in just before, or like close to it.
It was in the snowy place.
Oh, and there's also the whole...
puzzle...
with the...
with the music stuff.
One on the ledge, one under the sun, and one in the pond, and the last one I forget.
Where's the...
There was one...
I think there was one I never found, of those four.
Maybe it was the ledge one.
So, I tried going all the way here last time.
Oh, right.
That's right, I remember this.
Wait, something spawned here last time, remember?
Nothing's...
Wait, is that a sheep?
Dude!
We need polymorphine.
Okay, hold on.
Oh, dude.
This is big.
Oh, I never switched the screen either.
I'm sorry about that.
Hold on.
Polymorphine.
Uh...
Get...
poly...
Morphine.
And bring...
Oh my god, I can't...
Wait a minute.
Bring...
to...
stone...
west...
of...
lake, I guess.
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure something will happen there.
Okay.
Sorry if I'm not...
removing that overlay before.
Okay, now we have this thing.
I'm pretty sure that's a statue, or like, something in real life somewhere.
Oh, that one looks interesting.
Hello.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to see what would have happened.
And it looked like it had golden antlers, you know?
Like it was special.
Oh wait, this guy has a lot of HP.
Oh, right!
Hold on, there was something with the worm blood.
What does this do again?
You're seeing things more clearly.
Cause ingesting worm blood.
Look at my screen, it's all fucked.
Seeing things more clearly.
What do you mean?
Clearly in what way?
Oh shit.
Back, back, back, back, back.
Don't drown in that shit.
I wanna... I wanna eat more of this.
Eat it!
Can I not eat it when it's in the...
Oh, that's annoying.
I can't eat it while it's here.
But wait, I can fill it up.
My bottle.
It has worm blood in it now.
I'm gonna grab more worm blood.
There's definitely something going on there.
Look how it's collecting here.
Oh yeah, filled it up with worm blood.
Shit.
Okay.
Let's try that again.
Can I right click?
Dude, you're seeing things more clearly?
What's changing?
What am I seeing more clearly?
Oh wait, actually hold on.
Why is the water like this here?
This makes me intrigued.
Hold on.
This makes me think there's something down here.
Oh!
Essence of fire.
Your entire being is... Oh no.
Oh no, not this shit again.
What?
No, man.
Oh, fuck.
I had something like this.
Oh, at least it doesn't damage me.
Fuck me.
Essence of fire.
Fuck.
It's killing the fish.
You know what?
Since it doesn't damage me, maybe it's actually good in combat.
Oh dude, I just had an idea.
I'm digging.
I have an idea.
Essence eater?
Essence of fire?
Wait a minute.
Where?
Where was it?
Please tell me.
Will it eat my essence?
Will it remove it?
Oh shit, I forgot where it was.
It's gotta work.
It's an essence.
Oh shit, I'm on fire.
Okay, so this thing on me is not harmful.
I mean, it is harmful.
Oh no, I'm on fire again.
At least the worm blood sort of works there.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna die with this.
This better... This is the end of the run.
It's over, boys.
It's fucking over.
Oh, come on, please.
Ah,
I'm burning.
Oh shit, that was kind of loud.
I am so happy.
I'm so... Wait, what?
Am I still exploding?
No, wait, that was the wand.
My god, dude.
I thought my run was over.
I'm so happy.
Oh, that feels good.
I need... Oh, that feels so good.
I can't believe I didn't think about that the other time.
Remember when I picked up a similar one that also did this, but like in a smaller scale?
I ran around with that until I died.
And I'm pretty sure I found an essence eater before that.
I just didn't realize it at the time.
And that was so deep in a run as well.
Now I wonder what could have been that run, you know?
I think that was the run where I had one HP and I died in the lake.
Goddamn.
Well, that was cool.
Now I know that.
And then I can take this one too.
Okay.
Very good.
What's the sound in here?
I hear something here.
Oh, you know what?
Dude, this is the tree, right?
Let's try going... Oh wait, if we go below the tree, we're just going to end up in...
Let's see if I'm correct.
We're going to end up in collapsed mines, right?
I think.
Wait, where am I right now?
Yeah, this has to be collapsed mines.
No.
Wait a minute.
See what?
I mean, I know the roots of the tree are in the collapsed mines.
So I can't be... I must be right next to it.
Yeah, look.
Oh, I'm going to fill out the map, dude.
The reason I'm not going straight down, by the way, I'm scared of destroying the earth right below me so that I fall through and hit the beam itself.
That's why I'm doing it like this.
It's more safe.
Oh, you know what?
I'm going to test something real here.
Will it let me see things?
Please.
Oh my God!
Oh, shit.
Okay, okay.
It...
Discovery after discovery right now.
I don't even need to go through there.
I can dig.
I can finally explore it.
It gives me night vision.
Oh, look at the outline on the screen.
I didn't notice this before.
There's like an eye.
Anything else?
Yo.
What is that place?
Oh!
Oh my God!
Dude.
Listen to that music.
Hold on.
I need to see if there's more in here.
Oh, wait.
We got to eat one more.
I need to dig.
No, I need to...
Yeah, go here.
Let's go this way.
Dude, there's two hearts here.
That is phenomenal.
What else we got?
Oh.
Okay.
Gotcha.
So that's it, I guess?
I mean, not that I'm complaining.
Not that I'm complaining here.
Hell no.
Bro.
Are the stars aligning or what?
I'm going from one point to the next on my to-do list here.
Here we fucking are.
Let's see how powerful I am.
Oh, God.
Okay, they sort of die relatively quickly.
Look at that stuff.
Jesus!
It's bleeding copper!
Uh...
What about this?
Bro, what is going on?
Maybe it cannot die.
Maybe I have to avoid these things.
I mean, fine with me.
I'm a pro.
Let's go.
Teleportation.
Is that going to be teleported?
Boo.
Only living beings, I guess.
Dude, I can't believe the worm blood.
Oh, that's so...
Oh, my God.
It makes total... Now I understand.
That's why they put the worm eggs...
above this place.
Right?
You summon a worm?
Kill it?
Eat its blood.
Bam.
Bob's your uncle.
Oh.
Pheromone?
Oh, my God.
There's so much teleportation here.
Jeez.
Louise.
Okay, there's clearly... This looks like the head of a pig.
They are so creepy looking.
I can't hit shit.
Whoa.
Wait, am I blocking that entirely?
No, wait, right?
I blocked something, but I still took damage.
Jesus Christ, they bleed a lot of slime.
That's mana.
That's... I like mana.
I like mana.
I will drench myself in the mana.
Come here, buddy.
Why do you have that sign above your head?
Wait, that's a different sign.
Wait a minute.
Does that mean he does electricity?
Doesn't that look like an electricity sign, like something like that?
Oh, yeah.
Wait, was it that guy or this guy that just did that?
One of these just did electricity.
Yeah, look, look, look!
They indicate what spell they're gonna use.
Then we have one of these guys.
What are you trying to hit me with?
A spitterbolt, I think?
Okay, this place is not that bad.
I can fuck with it.
I like it.
Oh, but man...
It's been four, almost, oh my god, four hours and 40 minutes.
I gotta stop here, man.
Let's stop, as we say in Denmark, stop a mensläin a go.
It means, let's stop.
No, wait, quit while you're ahead.
That's the thing you say in English.
Let's quit while we're ahead and then come back and completely mess it up instantly next time.
So the Danish expression is stop when the playing is good.
If that makes sense.
Definitely means quit while you're ahead.
So what do you think about that, guys?
Finally, some progress today.
I feel like the last couple times, man, I was failing so hard I didn't discover shit.
This time, though, I didn't die once, by the way.
Wait, did I?
Wait a minute.
I did die once.
The first death doesn't count, right?
I actually kind of forgot about that.
But yeah, other than that, I nailed it.
I totally nailed it.
Today was awesome.
Exactly.
It didn't count.
The first time doesn't count.
Also, the drink that I opened the can.
I shit you not.
I only drank 20% of it and I completely forgot about the rest.
Because I was so immersed in this game from start to finish.
Four hours.
I didn't drink a single drop.
What the fuck is wrong with me?
I love that you guys love that new emoji that I put in.
It's just so hilarious seeing it everywhere.
Fungus and Joyer.
Exactly.
I did that too.
I did all of it.
I'm actually running out of things to try now.
I'm blaming it completely on the fact that I made a map.
You know, that must have been the thing that did it.
Cook tasty shroom and worm blood dish.
Fuck yeah.
Hell yeah, man.
I was tripping hard and I went on a hard trip.
A long trip down below and all the way to the top.
The essence eater blow.
My heart sank completely into my stomach.
As soon as I found out it was going to do that.
I thought, oh, that's it.
That's the end of the run.
I felt so terrible.
You know, because I had that experience last time of having that on me.
It was just the most annoying thing ever.
I was so relieved that I figured that out.
Oh yeah, good thing I had explosion immunity.
Yeah.
In fact, I think I had explosion immunity the last time I picked up one of those things as well.
Isn't that a funny coincidence?
Because I didn't take damage from that.
And that's not what ended up killing me.
But some other thing did, you know?
There was so much hype in the chat when you had the idea to go to the essence eater.
I kind of want to look at the VOD and see what you guys said in that moment.
It's so hype sometimes, those moments.
The other one wasn't explosive, if I recall correctly.
Oh, okay.
But I'm pretty sure I had explosion immunity because I remember thinking, oh, thank God I have it.
Otherwise I would be dead right now.
At this point, I'm getting spoilers from you.
Oh, thank you.
That's so awesome.
There are some spoilers on that moment around the... Yeah, I mean, I'm not going to look at the VOD.
I was just curious, you know?
I'm tempted, is all I'm saying.
But I'm definitely going to look at the highlight stuff when I'm done with this game.
Or when I'm mostly done, I would say.
This feels like the game you can never really be done with, you know?
Just hop in here and there, play a couple... Play a couple rounds, I would say.
But these rounds can take a while.
Summary cooking.
Yeah.
Okay.
Man, I feel so good.
That was such a great time.
Oh, man.
I have that exact same feeling now that I had in Rainworld.
When I...
Okay.
Quick spoiler here in case you haven't played the game.
Mute the stream for like 15 seconds, okay?
Mute now.
So when I found all the pearls and I brought them all together and got all the lore at the same time, that feeling is what I had this time.
Finding those things out.
What are you thinking about using?
Twitch, YouTube, both?
So, so far I have been streaming on YouTube for...
maybe a year before this.
It was good.
Although there is a bunch of limitations for me.
It's definitely a better viewing experience, for sure.
The fact that you can go back in real time, you can speed things up.
The VOD is instantly there when you're done.
But then there's also a bunch of drawbacks when it comes to modding.
So like moderators.
Also, it's way easier for me to set up the streams for reasons that I don't want to go into.
But just customizing the whole chat and every overlay and all the things I need is just so much easier for Twitch.
Because it's been around so long and everyone has made tools for it.
But so far, I would say I like both.
I think I like Twitch more.
Yeah.
At least so far.
Maybe one day I'll go back to YouTube.
It depends.
You know, maybe, who knows, maybe Twitch shuts down one day.
I mean, then I have no choice.
Me regrets.
Hey, man, I haven't seen you before.
I enjoy these streams so much.
It's an interesting dynamic you've got here.
Where the chat can only observe when you finally figure out features in this game.
It's a rewarding moment for chat as a whole and it keeps me hooked.
I'm glad to hear that.
I had the feeling that I think most people wouldn't enjoy this format.
Just because live streams are, I guess, supposed to be interactive by nature.
So it is definitely a weird thing I'm doing here, I understand.
But I'm glad to hear that some people are really enjoying that too.
I will do streams in the future where we interact more.
Especially for games that don't have many spoilers anyway.
But I definitely just enjoy immersing myself with the game and playing.
And it's really fun to know that people are watching at the same time.
Either fuming about the things I do or are like cheering me on, you know?
Makes me feel good.
It's really cool.
It's like I'm sharing my failures and also my successes with everyone.
That's right.
Twitch integration is also a thing with a lot of games.
You know, they have Twitch.
There's no such thing as YouTube integration.
It doesn't exist, unfortunately.
But I'm definitely going to try Twitch integration with Noita at some point, for sure.
It sounds fun.
Okay, hold on.
I'm going to raid someone now.
And then I have to eat something because I'm dying.
Again, we're going to raid someone from Noita who's streaming Noita.
Let's see who's streaming right now.
Red Riot Ross.
Or Light My Violet.
It's hot outside.
Let's cool down with Noita.
I like that.
Or Banger Video Outlet's Noita.
I'm going to raid Light My Violet.
Have fun.